Welcome to the night, the car is laid out for show Star shine is so bright, watch the
secrets unfold There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
with the rhythm
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
hearts in the balance
every garden open door
feel the romance
in every archangelord
destiny in twine
hi guys i'm back yeah there's a little annoying i think it was like uh so they're like
some like some like nuclear yeah not no no nasty it was it was last night
tonight it's just someone's threatening but yeah so there's a little monster it looks like it came
out of like a nuclear um well some nuclear waste must have fallen on like this uh this truck of mcdonald's
And then it created this kind of like pink, ugly,
really horrific bird with like the personality
of Steve Urkel and the charm, Steve Urkel.
And this thing, and it had this thing
where the voice box would never stop,
but it would just say nonsense.
It would just say stupid things.
And so then this person, I was nice to them,
oh, whatever, come on my piano, whatever.
Calls Christine a bitch
Says calls me tells me to shut the f up on my my show
Excuse me. No, I don't think so and so I kicked
You never saw them here before I don't know how they found their way over here. They were on beaters
I mean, but yeah, they they've been on a few times before
Yeah, they need to go back to the
The nuclear waste bin. It's just an unfortunate
I
Think it might be one of the last things left from Chernobyl
Okay
Yeah
It's crazy. It's crazy
Okay, so I have extra. How are you sweetie?
Electra got torn bombed by diamond last night
I mean, I'm not mad at Diamond.
I don't think I'll be able to have Diamond back on the show.
necessarily Diamond can be in the chat,
but the chat, YouTube did remove the video too.
But it wasn't her that it wasn't because it was because she
was stroking this like big inflatable dong under her dress
and then pulled and showed her boobs.
Okay, but
Oh lecture, would you like a car from this new inner worlds deck you got this easy sponsored this one you two removed it
And I did not get a strike. I did not
You bet. I thought I removed it like but I must have removed
Because sometimes it doesn't queue if I have the YouTube open it doesn't queue the live up on my channel until I
You love the new deck card. Okay, so yeah, but it's just like, you know
It's just not, you know
Not good. I was
Electra another miracle, right because I just hear hear people are form bombed in this video channel sticking down right away though, right this time
You know I never finished your video. I'm so sorry Jamie. Yeah, this is a solitary witness. I'm so sorry. We got interrupted it says
alone in the edge clarity
Draws under the
Moons glit gaze witness the truth then
Weave the insights back into your world. Yeah, I finished you Jamie. This was this was yours. This was the solitary witness, okay?
That's like be almost like it looks like she's in her going through some inner
Intermeditations and just relaxation reminds me a lot of the hermit. Okay, so this is for like for next. Okay next is for Electra
Electra you got this between worlds and this is really cool. It's like kind of surrealists are
Let's say Salvador dolly a little bit, right?
Maybe it is it says the between worlds and it says
section, intersection, threshold, multiple perspectives,
contemplation, co-existing realities, contrast,
awareness, and focus.
And it says,
poise at the edge of perception,
you witness the meeting of inner worlds,
observe the contrast,
therein lies understanding.
Yeah, and so we're in we are in between all these worlds and they're we're between this there's a world of the solids
There's a world of the air. There's a world of the fire the Sun. There's a world of the
You know the earth, right?
There's all these all the elements all brought together in this place, right including us where we are also these
So we're we're between we're a part of all of them. We're in the do you like that man's
Electra and Nancy would you like a card because I have these oracle cards. They just say a one card little oracle read
Have hopefully a great message for you or anybody else. Hi guys. Yeah, so that bird of character is no
Totally totally band that it's Elvador dolly. Oh, you're welcome. Yeah, I love Elvador dolly
melting clocks and
Yeah
You would love that. Okay, got you Nancy. This is for Nancy
Oh Nancy, so this one says facets in focus. Okay the facets and focus
Okay, it says
inner alignment
focused intention
internal coherence unified energy shared goal collective inner strength
filtered perception
And it says, Behold the power when your inner self's gaze as one.
Focus, sharpen, energy converges towards a shared horizon.
I hope you like that.
Hope you like that. Did you like the card lava? Did I tell Cheyenne Benny had pictures of Hirana?
Is Cheyenne okay tell Benny that Cheyenne seems to have a little I don't
I can't figure it out. She's oh you did. Oh, thank you. Oh great. I love it. Thank you
Pleasure to be reading Baphomet
I think Cheyenne's a little bit a little bit on the cuckoo. Okay, I don't mean I don't know no shade
Okay, she's a nice person. She's now she's over there telling Benny that I say that he has pictures of pyro
Oh, what is going on, please?
Yeah, she's just a little nuts. I didn't say anything like that. I don't know what she's bases, but I did say
You know, I was talking about blade and how
Blade had posted a picture of Piranha on my discord, you know, and I delete and it was deleted
She's telling Piranha that oh my god
Can you just tell tell Piranha that I'll explain it or you know, it would go everything is fine
I hope I don't mind I didn't share the story but it is kind of like a story that I think can help people like you shouldn't be
Sending anything that you don't want on the internet to get out of the internet to anybody on the internet because it will
Yeah
Thank you back a bathroom it appreciate it let the hang out. Thank you so much. Good to see you again, too. Hi Lava
Yeah, we got some I got this deck ready if anyone's awesome. Thank you so much bathroom it
Yeah, I love Piranha, and I saw her at Benny's, and she came on the show today.
We had a great time, and I think she's liking the vibe of the show.
So, you know, things will, like, there'll be signs like that.
Like, some people will disappear, and like, then a lot of what you can do with you and
the show changes, and then next, then some people will come back, and I mean, it's like,
Things will happen and not necessarily saying, you know, it's gonna all gonna be good things and I'll be or any all gonna be bad things or anything. It's just
You'll see different effects as it kind of just shifts the whole universe when you
Right, okay, you like Piranha the Piranha. Hey Mimo we're doing some
One card pulls from this new Oracle deck I got today and then if you'd like to
Perhaps
Get a more detailed reading you can see the info here
I'll tell you everything you need to know
Yeah, Mimos here your bestie good
Yeah, it's unfortunate though that means that people like burdo. I mean this person is just insane. I
Mean, I don't know. I don't know there anything about there. I don't care who they are. I don't I don't want to bother them
I don't want to harass them
Just get a life
You can sit there and scream on panels nobody understands the word you said nobody really cares what you say
They just use it to use it to annoy new people to like kind of haze them
Even music is Marty figured out. There's nothing to do with you except, you know get bored with you in 10 seconds
You don't know
25 minutes till oh, what's gonna happen?
Santa coming
What are you doing? Why is there a maraca?
What are you doing? Are they there's a satanic hand sign to the satanic? What's going on Nick Nick satanic your state?
Maybe
Joe July 7th finally off bail bonds. Oh, oh like that's tomorrow. Oh, okay
25 minutes. Oh, so it's almost there 935
Is it gonna be a private freak-off for you and me be after the show and you know anybody else can be there, but
It's getting
This you ask me personally
Hey, Lola, I
Just don't know hold on
Hold on. I think he just went to the MBA and hold on a second.
Okay, so I unblocked you in the chat. Let's go to the chat. You can talk to me from the chat right now
Hi Beatles juice. Good to see you Beatles juice. Hi a beetle. I got a new deck. Would you like a card from the new deck?
It's a Oracle deck, so it's like a we're doing little one-card reads off of it. Good to see you
Miss you Beatles juice
It's been a while
Since you came to my chair and asked for a card
It's been a while since I've been streaming. This is like hour number 21 or something. What are we doing guys?
Who wants the card? Nick, do you want a card? Can I pull a card? I'm gonna do it.
I'm not all one of you cards for cards for everybody. I mean cards are really nice
Now these beautiful nails see look
So good when I do the reading
Uh-oh
Sure, I got you beatle
Beetle juice
You know you got this this is poise presents and it kind of looks like you a little bit probably
Yeah, and you guys gotta look like you look at the nice spot. Okay, and there's the poise presents. It says
It says quiet
Observations, self-awareness, calm presence, inner stillness, composure, hidden in depth, pause before action.
It says, stillness sparks unions when wielded with awareness.
Your your quiet gaze builds worlds observing
the unfolding moment
From a place of inner calm
Okay, it's pretty sweet. I don't know if you met somebody or it looks like a cute kind of like you're gonna have like a lot of confidence
I don't know if you have a date or something or you're with this girl
We have a lot of confidence and you're just like peaceful and serene and happy even being being quiet together. I don't know
Hope that made sense for you
See I did I blocked you test it. It's a 666. It's the only one I saw for you
Let's come back a little bit. I'm just I'm opening up the show. I'm just like having a quiet little
Trying to get everyone in here
But I
Don't I will never go into somebody's chat
Say hey, I'm having his live right now come come on my life. I'll never do that
But I can't promise that I won't be on the same time as other content creators
I can't worry worry about what time other people are going on or if I go on then someone I can't even
You're welcome beetle I got about I just I just feel like that. I don't know if you're with that
I don't know about your romantic life, but it looks like it's a
Cute cute happy pairing. Hey bsr or bsbb if you'd like a reading tonight. Let me know
I got one card free oracle readings tonight and
Then like more cards. I do have the writer deck the gold writer deck
Do a couple paid reading options
11 people. Yeah, but it was a great day. Thank you so much, Beedle. Thank you. You're a stud. Thank you my
My dude, thank you so much. Appreciate that any time
Beedle took my viewers
No, she didn't like you know, be the head about the same amount of viewers
She has now and I met her and I had I had like not many viewers
I made it. I was just doing live streams not panels. I had maybe 10 20 people
She introduced me to so many people. I mean, there's so many and that's why she might she might get mad because she has done a lot
And maybe I haven't like thanked her enough because she did so much for me starting out and it's like
You know, and I don't want to take viewers from her or have that feeling
You can't believe I finally got Benny to accept a sexuality. What's the clicking noise? I don't know. Let me see
Yeah, that's pretty cool. It wasn't it though Joe hold on
do you hear me now it was a good panel of things joe yeah great yeah it was fun i'm
on mute again what's going on it's my right hello testing it looks like it's on is it working
do you hear me now
if it doesn't work i could use oh it sounds better okay
good yeah so it was a good panel like I went on and Benny was like he knows who
I am he's like he's so like he's just cool we're hanging out with Chris K me and
Benny and this is chatting and it was funny like I was like Benny you get you
get you gave birth to me into the into the panel verse you brought me in he's
like well I'm glad I can make your YouTube wishes come true
So I and I really do hope because you know, and he knows exactly there's a night like where he started talking about
Just something very controversial. There's a lot of people like why are you why are you?
Uh, oh like a paranoid. Why do you care like about just talking about this and this because I was at Benny's one night
And first he started doing a rap and he's trying to rap like a gangster or something and he just started saying the n-word a lot
And I was like, whoa, it's kind of like he said it a lot of times then he got onto some controversial topic
I'm not even gonna tell you what it is or we're gonna try to say it on the show, but I talked about a controversial topic and
Or he talked about a controversial topic
He said the next day 5,000 of his subscribers was down by 5,000 and he was shadow band
So
That's why I freak out sometimes. I don't want to be shadow band
It's not it's not easy because he had like a hundred people in his chat. He went down to like 10 20 people in his chat and
you know
If you can just like, you know, and if it's at least that's his channel
So if he says it, he's like, oh well
I said it on my channel if people are saying shit on my channel and my channels hurt from it from how other people are saying because
They just can't control themselves
I'll just suck and I think it might the algorithm has been affected or else maybe people are just sick of me
I'm on look quite a bit, but
Okay, I'm good Nick do you want a card who else anybody else in here anybody here Joe BSRB
Thanks, butyl
Mimo anybody here
Is anybody out there?
Anybody
Aw, yeah, I miss Beetle, too.
Beetle.
Yeah, it's been a lot of drama, Beetle.
I think you miss, I think you, like, I don't think
you enjoy the drama, and so it's probably not a big deal
that you miss some of it.
I think you came at a better time.
Drama's gotten a little bit better, I guess, a little bit.
As in it's not as nasty as it was I mean in it being drama you think oh drama you know drama's fake
There's this is drama
It was like it shouldn't it shouldn't be things that people are worried about fretting about getting upset about an extreme
But you know, but they act it out. Sometimes we do that with things in the world, right?
Let's go easy. I got the deck. Would you like a do you like a car from the new deck easy?
You can come on panel or I'll do it from the chat, but here's the deck
Very unassuming unassuming I love the colors, so that's blue
orange and
Off-red and these are Oracle cards
You just woke up cool. Sorry about earlier
No, I get a little bitchy, right
I'm sorry
Hi everybody, yeah
That was a it was a good 18 hour stream I did easy I had to private it
because that
that uh, what's that carry?
BIR do I'm not gonna pronounce his name again. He's banned now, but he
Was like hello kiss. He's like your channels your channels
Going to be deleted soon or something. He's like your chance be like or something great. I don't know trying to threaten me and shit
The burrow can go
Sit on a egg and twist, okay
Thank you, thank you guys
Yeah, that's an interesting conversation. I did catch a little bit of
Be the show not to like, you know, and I didn't say anything in chat because I'm not gonna like
Changed the topic and whatever but
Couple one thing I won't I won't criticize anything. I'll say I don't want to criticize her. I'll say one thing Ciggy
Ciggy
Ciggy no
See yeah, I knew there was something I knew there's I just knew there was something about you see
What you said to her how much about her cat
If I ever if I ever hear something like that come out of your mouth. Oh my god, I
Should just like
Should be like an instant band. I bet I know you were like it's a bit. It's not funny. It's not funny like what you said
Or in you it's like not I don't know. It's not a troll. It's not it's just all it is is hurtful. It's just like sick
Okay, and I love her cats
So do not ever not fuck with our cats, okay
Not good is he not good
And I agree with her decisions like she went she's talk to your girlfriend to make sure you got some total
Psychopathic asshole. I'm not sure you're not
Hey, she and are you going over there? And you told them you tell Piranha that I was saying
Benny has pictures of her say and just don't repeat. Are you repeating stuff because that's not the story
You're just like you're causing problems with Piranha and stuff. You just think you know, I wasn't that wasn't like
You didn't tell you didn't retell the story right and now people are confused and I'm getting people say what happened
So you just make sure you if you repeat something make sure you get it correct, okay?
You think you misunderstood, okay?
Okay, I
Don't know can that it can a mod can a mod check out Cheyenne's account and just see what's what's going on there
Report back to me, please
Please if you can't see me
It's okay. No, you're fine. You're fine. I just don't want to
People are like, oh, what's he's talking about? You know, you said like a document there
Yo, what's up, how are you doing? Yo, can you hear me?
Yes, can you hear me? What's uh, what it is? What do you do?
Are you doing? How's your night? I'm okay. Oh, it's going wonderful
Are you having a drinky tonight? I'm in the
Yeah
Mm-hmm. I just had one shot though. I've just barely started just now
Yeah, I have uh, well I have like another
Harder lemonade tall boy and a half
so
I think that should be good for me, and I have a couple of the get the talkies Fuego
When sandwiches the blue ones
The blue
The lemon ease of this one. This is a strawberry pineapple right here. No, I mean, oh, I mean the talkies
Sorry, oh the talkies. Oh, it was like they take basically
It's a like a chicken breast with like the it's like
It's like the color of talkies the girl with chicken breast and talkies
I think I might have a cheese in it too, and it's just on a bun. It's really good. It's pretty good
It's just why I wouldn't get one free. You can get the chicken chicken battered in talkies
Yeah, it's like the batter is like the color. It's color is talkies. It's good. Thank you. What did I say?
So I was I was you know Benny is thing or you know Benny is or no, are you familiar?
I think that's a pretty general name
Benny Benny Benny Blanco IP2
Hmm. Yes, I'm familiar with him. Okay, so I was just over on his panel and it was cool
I would go you know who else was there when I wait when I got there. Isn't he like
Pretty young
Yeah, he's 24 or 23, but you know who was there on the show when I got there
No, yes Chris K
Yeah, he was just he was just on my show last night Chris K was on my show last night
You know Chris K Chris K. He was just on my stream and people were trolling him and he rage quit. Oh shit
Well, I like Chris he did like he was like telling someone in the chat
What was it guys now? I forgot the guys in the chat
But I think it was somebody named ghost but it's not crucible ghost and he was like ghost was like this guy ghost was like
Well, he was hearing some of Chris's stories or Chris's like yeah, I beat up this person
I got this fight get this fight and he's again. You should you should totally share if you've been clips
You should totally share your clip on the channel
And he's like, yeah, I got clipped.
And he's like, I got clipped.
And then he's like, I got, you know,
I got to fight with this homeless guy, blah, blah, blah.
I was like, okay.
And then they're like, put it on, put it on.
I was like, I don't want to put a clip on.
So then I was like,
Played it myself. They would just posted the link in the chat
It's him going up to like a tent like on the side of like a bridge or something and he like starts
He goes into that he's like please please please and he starts knocking on the tent of the tent flap
And then he like pulls this guy out. He's like, oh get the fuck out of here. You see them. You see now
Okay, well
I watched that and then the guy and the guy ended up like, you know, hitting him or something, but
that doesn't, that doesn't sound, yeah, I've spoken to him about that, that's not a good idea.
Yeah. I mean, I, every time, every time he says these things, like I tell him, I'm like, what,
you like, you want to go back to prison? Like you talk about how bad it is, but then you're
doing all of these things. Sounds like you want to go back, like, do you miss somebody there or
Like come on. He was pretty shocked. You know one of the things he was like I was like, oh, hey
Like no, I mean, I don't I don't get Chris K. He you know
When he's not on this stream, he always talks about how much he hates f-words his words not mine
And so then I'm like I look at streams and then he's here talking to you a you know
homosexual and say
Eight hours, and I hate f-words. I hate f-words so much
Oh, I would eat the shit out of an effort his words not mine
I know but he said he would do an only fans
Collaboration with me if I could like find a find a woman
I mean, that's crazy. Let's call the devil's threesome. Let's discuss. He said I could do a devil's
I would never do that. You're gonna do that. I would never do anything like that
I'm not down to share my with me with me. Oh with me. No, no, I'm not down to share my woman
I'm good. No, I'm not sharing your woman
But it's like, you know, both of us. What if it was like you if you weren't with your wife random bitch
I don't care about. Yeah, still I don't want to do that. Cheers
Cheers. Oh, well, well, I guess things not gonna come. Well, it's just gonna be me and Chris better get the double beds
You have to hire somebody else. Yeah, I'm gonna hire anybody. I'm gonna I'm gonna charm charm some did you hear about the diddy case
What do you think about them?
Uh, I think he's like kind of like just like a little middleman in the whole big thing
Like he has probably some white billionaires behind
Behind the whole thing that I'm telling what to do. He's like this black, you know, what kind of hip-hop guy easy to take the fall
I don't know if it's consensual. I don't know if it's like, you know, he's really in prison
I don't know what's really going on, but I think that if um,
Sorry, you're saying it's I up. I think you're right about that
If it was there is there has to be somebody above him that the the courts are protecting because if it was just him
I think he would just be the full guy a hundred percent. They would just take him out
Yeah
And I don't know how long you'll actually spend if people are saying oh he's going to prison for sure or whatever
It looks like it looks like some people are saying he might get out on the time served. Yeah, but I
Think it's really weird
You know, there's got to be some there's there's probably some witness or not witness, but I'm
Jerry tampering
I mean, there's there's got to be some Jerry tampering
It seemed like most of America was on agreement that did he's a weirdo
So I can't understand why the Jerry would vote in his favor
Well, it's like, you know, the jury will look at very specific, you know, you know how jurors work
They look very specifically at every like little detail about things and it's like an explain in certain ways
There could be jury tampering as well or the jurors are paid off, you know, who knows but
You know
Just because he's weird and he probably did weird things at parties I like I think they need specific evidence of
Certain things to charge because America's you know Americans don't really understand it here like little details
That's you know blows most people's minds, right?
What am I when am I smoking and smoking a little? Oh, these are little vapes
Little weed vapes
So
Anyway, I'm not sure
We got here yo
What up? What up? What up? King. Hold on. Would you like a I got my new cards easy
Would you like a card from your new card deck? Just the Oracle card
Okay, yeah, okay here we go
This one okay, so this one for you easy this is quiet allure, okay
Okay, and it says
It says, subtle magnetism, quiet confidence, self-possession, authentic presence, inner
world, gentle allure, comfortable being.
Rises not from effort, but from that quiet confidence of simply being authentically you. I'm sorry
I stumbled a little bit, but yeah, I think it's like I think this is like, you know
You have to also got this innocence. You got this inner child that you look at the world
That's why it's like that and you're and you're able to oh
It's very cute
Yeah
So young easy now ziggie ziggie me wants to see one of our shit
Okay, say these are just Oracle cards. Is that okay if I pull you on him say it or no just one they're real quick
Okay, I
Don't know who this hood rat sounding guy is but I'm not Ziggy
Okay, yeah, I'm sure that you've spoken the other I'm sure you're spoken of the
No, you said thank you
Ziggy is the other guy. Hey, so there's so sick. This is for you
This is the quiet within and then there's like, you know, he's up this
He's like on the cliffs. I'm kind of that was a Abraham Lincoln
No, he's like a no male Mary Poppins
Maybe maybe maybe what the hell but it says
This is interquiet stillfulness presence binding center calm observation
self-connecting
intersanctuary
Core being it says
Deeper than thought quieter than breath
Lies the silent steady core of your being
Return their presence awaits. Okay, and so this is basically that means
Well, I would say it means go into yourself and go into the quiet still place
That is a soul and like, you know be able to calm your mind
Think you probably are in perspective is something that I've always been good at. Oh, yeah, because and introspection is not easy for everybody
Especially people that are like heavily
Narcissistic they tend to not want to like look into themselves. They're actually afraid of like inside of themselves
They're obsessed without my piece of shit
No, I don't care about it. Yes. That's what it is
Okay, well, I'm a piece of shit
Well, I hope you enjoyed your reading stick. Have a good
Can you read another card? Yeah another card. What do you want a card another card? Can you show the shuffle?
Yeah, please
I'm asking please kind of
I mean, I believe you it's just it's just like part of the experience. You know what I'm saying
Part of the experience is going to be the shuffling right like you're you go to casino you see themselves in the cards
Okay, I got you. I got you. Yeah, some people like some people like that is sometimes harder for me to
Show it to the camera. I'm not like great at like playing like that. But I'll try okay. I got you see you
Oh, okay. Yes. Okay. This card's coming for you. Okay, so say here's your card
This says wild crown
Okay, wild crown, so there's an interesting,
it looks like a, is that you?
No, I don't know, I'm just kidding.
It says wild crown, it says wild creativity,
blooming ideas, unconventional beauty, unique wisdom,
structure versus freedom, inner garden and vibrant thoughts.
It says even from ordained paths, wild beauty,
Blooms where your crown of unique thoughts with pride it is
Magnificently yours, so you got that wild my already do
Yeah, there we go. Oh, and nobody make me feel bad for what I say and think we'll keep going
It's saying you know, that's you maybe I'm an independent spirit
So me some of you niggas can't understand that well, I understand I feel always feel like I'm a
I'm an independent contractor. I think that's the word for it
But it's like kind of like the spirit world. Hi guys. Hey spunky. Hey Justin Gotti here
What's up? I'm Gotti. It's just like I'm an independent journalist. Did you want one more card easy make it even?
Okay
Okay, I'm sorry. I hope you feel better, you know
Drink some uh take effect on my body. Oh
Yeah, I
Think the voodoo rangers, you know kind of sort of changing me a while
Those motelos you need a huge a card for a future reading for your butthole. Oh my god
Okay, come on up spunky. We're doing a butthole reading. Yeah, we're doing a butthole reading
Yeah, yeah, that's crazy but whole reading. Okay. Okay. Let's go you fuck a freak
Yeah, you can tell me my butthole psyche. Okay. Let's see. Let's see. Hey, here you go
Oh
This is this is like see there it is right there
Yeah. She's in there. You can't beat this. You can't beat this. He said she said let me get a ball reading. It says real shadow. Look at this like the light coming out of the butthole. See it? Yeah.
It says, it says shadow integration, power and darkness, owning full spectrum, regal presence, strength, direct awareness, embracing unconventional aspects. It says owning shadow. Aspects! Aspects!
Aspects, keep your pecs on the ass, yeah.
So it says, own your shadows with dignity.
They hold the keys to your hidden kingdom.
And the throne of your, the throne,
your throne where you sit, right?
Of your authentic power.
So there you go.
The throne of our authentic powers, thank you.
Yeah.
That was kind of perfect.
The power, the power is the power.
The power.
My buddy, I'm staying away from your butt, Spunky.
I don't know what's gonna happen.
I don't know.
I think it's the entrance to the new world.
No, this is not my butthole, Virginia.
Or she's got to use the power of her butt.
Somebody's gonna wanna, like, yo, babe.
Somebody's gonna be like, hey, can I put it in your butt?
She's gonna be like, hmm, the power of the butt.
Let me see.
What can I do with this?
Well, Justin, but yeah, Spunky,
these needs to twerk for Justin.
Learn to twerk for Justin, okay?
Maybe go to a class.
Oh, yeah.
That sounds like she has a flat ass.
I do.
Let me ask you, have you got lucky with the booty yet, homie?
Homie, did you get lucky with the booty yet?
Yeah, Justin you're lucky with the booty. Yeah, not yet. No, but I'm working on it
It's coming out as you see from the car
Oh my god, I just saw the I just saw the KY jelly car, okay
And it says start with one pinky and that's what it says
Oh my god, yeah, teach him the way he's saying it.
You were Gaudi, but maybe you should call Carmel
for the butt action.
Oh, no.
Oh, Gaudi.
Guys, we're going to have an orgy by the end of this year.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm talking about Gaudi and me.
No, I'm just kidding, I'm not.
Who?
What did I just say?
Thanks.
OK, wait.
I didn't say anything.
Stop talking like that.
I think SIG said something disgusting.
OK.
Okay, time to
You should go out for the butt action
Uh-oh, who's who's that? Oh, yeah, that's Justin. Yeah
I don't know who was talking about butts yesterday. Someone was like there was like I think we were going into such
Obscenity those guys come in the room from the bar. No, yeah, I don't think I never saw them. I don't think no
Maybe I wasn't their type, but I think I was funny that they're funny. They're pretty cool. They were super excited
Yeah
All right, I'm look I think if I was to meet them I
Don't know. I think I have a little bit more
more charisma than I I
Used I used to I think
If you and I went to the bar we we'd pull him some serious tail. I
Think so. I just think
I'm bad. I'm bad at places alone, you know, but uh, no, man, you and me would be like amazing
I would put you in so much ass. Oh my god. Well, let's do it
Carmel would do it. Oh, Justin said Carmel would do it
I don't know is this guy Carmel?
Carmel is like some ex-fuck buddy of Justin's that Goddy knows about so
Okay. Wow. Oh, she's a woman.
Carmel's a woman. Okay.
Carmel's a woman.
Yeah.
I was thinking, I was thinking he was a man.
I was like, oh, this is a Carmel guy.
Gaudi and Justin have been friends for many years.
Well beyond my time of being around.
Yeah, I don't, but did you see Ziggy on, uh, on beatas tonight?
Like what happened?
No, I did not. What happened?
Um, she was like, you know, she like let him on and he was like, you know, she was hesitant
to because he kicked them off for show before and then
She was like she went outside showing her cats and stuff like that
You know, I love her cats and then she went to one and he's like he's like he's like I would I would
SHOT that cat in the head or something like that. Whoa
And so yeah, and so she hung up on him got really upset and then
Then he kept trying to come back on and then she's like she's like I won't talk to you until I talked to Jan
And I find out you're not some like
It's like psychopath, like she was like upset, but it was just it was a kind of shocking, especially I talked to him yesterday
He was like very nice. He also said he was like
Asked her to play a song when she was DJing and he was a song about like satanic
Animal sacrifices. I was just like like really disturbing stuff, right?
Well, he was telling me like yesterday
Like that he was this that he was a Satanist and stuff and then but then he was like he told page
He's like page
You're you read the Bible and you're not supposed to be if you're fortune telling and he was a immense page
It's like I'm not a Christian and he was like accusing and she got real upset
And like he was just kind of nasty to page and stuff and that was just I know I wasn't on the show
they must be they must be on another platform all right sake let me tell you if anybody's nasty
a page they ain't good people yeah they ain't gonna last long they ain't gonna last long
But yeah, she was like she was almost in tears. She was like she's like I'm not I'm not a Christian
She's like I never said as a Christian like yeah
Yeah, he was like and he's like boy
He's like you you have to stop doing that because you can't do cards as he's a come to our side
Yeah, somebody came to a pace of my oh you're Christian
Pregils the other day about the same shit
Well, there's gonna be a prayer readers. There's gonna be a lot of religious nuts like I was Emma's mod and she of course
She has they even like more of the she had Emma's like looks like a like a demonic succubus
They don't got Christian terror readings. Yeah, they do they have their Bible decks
They do and it's like also in the Bible or something about, you know
Big more like fortune tellers like that are like making predictions. I got like a profit type of prediction. That's different
fortune tellers
Glitches
connections
All guys in the same place and if they mad they don't got the talent to fuck them
Right, I mean it's like it's basically saying, you know
If you're gonna be guided they try to go go for the highest highest source right because there are
I'm sorry, I'm the most rude when I wake just oh
Okay, no problem, dude
Yeah, oh here we go
There we go
You look up Steven Tyler's beat picture. Why would he want to see that?
It's Steven Tyler, I mean not the best-looking man
Dude looks like a lady. Is Steven Tyler really a woman? Wouldn't that be a plot twist, right?
Wait, ask Justin. Whose feet are prettier, mine or Steven Tyler's?
How he knows how pretty Steven Tyler's feet look. He always looks like he prunes on a
he
prunes on a
bamboo. Bamboo steward. Oh, it's feet. Okay
Yeah, well, maybe he needs a pedicure
I'm not sure a pedicure could help that
Stephen Tyler, I mean it's like oh, he was there for odds. Well, isn't he like, you know, like 90 years old now
Tiffany has a picture of my big toe. Oh, oh, but there isn't that detached from your body gotty body gotty
No, isn't it attached from your your rest of your foot and don't mind the music in my car
He he's but God he said he like he took home the big toe and you like put it in a in a soup
And then he like ate off all the meat off of it and then he did something with the bone
I remember that guy you told me you did that
right
You ate your own toe. That's sick
God he's nasty. Yeah, I am son. We're defining shit
Oh, it's on me. Let me see. Why would I married? Okay, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, hold on
Maybe oh, oh, yeah, okay. I don't know. I guess I guess it was an appropriate question
It was it was an appropriate question. I can't hear the song and not diamond do backflips, right?
God if you haughty. Yeah, so the one inspired me doing my my pretzel and my speedo's
Was when flirty diamond put her legs behind her head on when she was on a table and she's somersaulted off the table
it was
Whatever happened with forty diamond and I is my karma for laughing until I peed my pants over that
I'm not happy. I'm not proud of it
Oh my god, it was the best. It was like the funniest thing. Probably the funniest thing I saw in like the last 10 years
No, I'm talking about
Yeah, what's really diamond did it pretty diamond did a somersault on a table and like a short skirt when she flipped over you could
Like oh my god. We just googled Steven Tyler's feed. Have you seen?
Yeah, I don't want to look at it. I don't like that
Oh my god. Oh my god. Wait, let's take it off. Why are they yellow? What color are they?
They look yellow. Look at them. Yellow? You see? Oh my god. Why is a big toe so big? Hold on.
It's not so big. It's so crazy. It looks like there's no other toes.
They're running away from the other ones.
They don't want toes wrapping around the other one yellow. They just yellow psyche. They just he oh my goodness
Yeah, yellow of white. That's disgusting. Oh
Toes on top of the big toe
Yeah, well, you know what sometimes that's genetically possible. I think but you know what?
He can go to this show called my feet are killing me. They go through the worst feet
I see them literally take a like a saw like and like
And like this guy's it's like a wood saw and this guy's they the pieces of his the calisthenes are coming up like wood chips
Obviously and his toes are all curled over. They like I'll have to show you sometime, but
Very good. Thank you for sharing that. Oh my god
And I was married. I didn't know if it was a thing. I was focused on your marriage unlike some girls. Okay. Well
God, how many how many of your toes have you eaten? I want to know that you can't hear the yeah diamond
You don't find the link
30 diamond
Oh my God. Oh my God. Here. Put up you for a second. I have me in a person. Uh-oh. We're talking about some private, private, sexy stuff.
Thank you. How many people we got in the building? Because all the cameras I'll be telling you about, they have to run it right now and all those haters is over there right now. That's where I'll be here.
That's why it's a little slow right now. Oh, I know. Yeah.
There's something that and I'm definitely not talking about Peter. This is open right now, too
But I didn't go okay, but the other panel if he
Oh, okay, let me see if it comes up with my
All right, I'm back. Hi, let me see if they come just reading. Um
Comments are in the chat and made me laugh
You know, I think I had a dream about uh, uh, uh, something about reading or that
And then I said, I woke up and said, you said, you said that that came in.
Oh yeah.
I just, and it just picked it up in the show started.
So you, I just brought it in when you came up pretty much because you're
watching.
I just, you're being a pervert stuff off.
Yes
Sparky you want to talk freaky you want to go all these fucking no life fucking jerk off internet jerk off
They literally jerk off. They like over there. Sparky's here. Sparky's here. Oh, can they all get in on amp right now?
Oh, Justin said you're right
Well, you know, I know I'm like I'm like the
I'm like the gay friend that actually likes Spunky for her.
Aw, you have a psyche as my gay friend who actually likes me for me.
Uh, psyche, you remind me so much of my friend that I had my whole life that has passed.
Like, I met you and I was like, I'm in love with him. Stop picking on him.
That's what I told everybody.
All right, she's a little chubby but not as now think bigger than her about say something whatever she saw she talks
Yeah, fucking it's personality. I just talk so fucking freaky all the time
Yeah, are you freaky you're freaky spunky that might be me that might be me
Every little conversation got a little do it though dirty day a little. Yeah, just like just a little sprinkle of it
Right
But like enough to let you know, I'm down, right?
Person but you got a slutty thotty mind
It's a perfect balance
You got that duality with that, you know the duality card, right? I think it was you there's a car that says
Oh, that was I think it was Theresa never mind, but a lot of the cards have the similar meaning which is like balance
They balanced in with it, but I love my butthole card. My butthole card was the best
Yeah, no, no, well, we are going to make it. What was it dark or something something dark?
It was it was uh, it's regal shadow or something or the regal shadow. Yeah
And so it's like and it said you're thrown. It said you sit on the throne. You sit sit on my throne
Yes, exactly
Everybody's gonna call out the boy card the butthole card the wriggle throne is the but
Oh
Yeah, wait, I don't know. Yeah, what's your name in this chat?
Let's be easy. Oh
Easy, I love you easy
Yeah, thank you. No, I know you are
Yeah
Hannah, okay. Oh, come on. God. Yeah. Look at this ugly guy. This is the ugly guy
You're beautiful
Does ignore him Hannah, please
You can't hurt you here. No one can hurt you here, Hannah
Got any of the same power if you like sort of fighting you would both think
There'd just be a draw your wrenches are exactly the same power
I wasn't gonna argue with nobody are you sure how I ignore this psyche? I'm not stupid
All right. Yeah, well, I'll stir the pot of those sometimes. I know how to ignore arguments. I know how to
Give them what they want or just
It's my father and me swipe major psycho
Yeah
Easy do you have a woman on here or no?
What happened you have a woman on here? No, my wife don't be on YouTube. No, okay
I felt like I thought maybe there was or like I heard you had a woman or
No, no, no, I got a wife and kids. Yes. My wife came on YouTube once
And then she was like, no, I don't want to do what you have fucking community or do this shit.
And I'm, I'm all right. I'd rather listen to you and laugh.
Yeah, Justin probably feels the same way.
And see you here?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Now he's sad. Now he's sad to introduce me.
Well, Justin got the right idea because some people just sit down and listen and they enjoy listening and laughing.
Is Justin naked on the bed because his head propped up?
He had his head propped up. He has boxers on and the blanket on.
Okay.
Is that scratching his junk?
What do you guys want me to say that?
Yo, spunky. Tell him to stand up and make it clap.
And I'm not talking about his cheeks.
Make it clap Justin. Oh, I know Justin. He's not going to make it clap. You know how to do it. Did you hear him?
I hear it. I hear it.
Justin's response was oh, I have many times. Oh
Okay. No, come on, Gotti. Come on.
Gotti said he's going to do a smudge bath right now,
but he'll come up after.
Okay.
Gotti, when you get out the tub, you got to make it clap.
He's not in the tub.
Yeah, he has a Filipino male nurse.
No, it's an Nigerian nurse's aide,
and she's going to make it clap.
Okay.
And Gotti married her.
Gotti married her, he said.
Oh, my God. That's perfect.
What a perfect setup.
Yeah, I'm kind of sad because I kind of like Goddy more, but whatever, you know, if he doesn't want to wait for me, it's fine. Oh
Goddy when you get on panel, can you make it clap five times?
Goddy just just just clap one hand instead of one hand
Wow, I'm not sure he has control of any hands, so
I'll let him use my hand. I'll let him use my yeah. Yeah, I'll make I'll make the clap for you, baby
He got real mad when I said I was on the stick up hot dog for the 4th of July at my butt and then
Turn it up and put it down his feeding tube. He didn't like that
Well, let me let me correct what Katie's trying to say she's trying to say my wife came on panel
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, she came in on my name show the cheeks. I was riding my dick
Yeah, I know I know it's probably here, but I think you know this person Katie. I guess she knows you
Oh, that's pretty cool. He married his Nigerian nurse's aid
Okay, make it up. So yeah, that's awesome. Hey mom make it clap
Make it clap and when God he gets here, we're gonna hit him on make it clap. We want to hear Goddy when you get up here
Yeah
I got that from Instagram
Some some female I think it was a video of the female shoes like oh look I'm clapping
And he's like you're not the only one and then he spread his legs. He's like
My god
Look big he's dying right now
You that she was hilarious. I was like, oh shit. Just make it clap. That's done. That's why I got it from just make it clap
should tell them how many times you get hit on per day.
Oh, my, no, Justin, we're not going to tell them about that.
How many times do you get hit,
or a seven you get hit on per day, I would say.
Yeah, I get hit on a lot, so that's a bar.
Look, he doesn't know whether I told you the story, guys.
Tell us
Well, the story at the bar when I was like, oh, yeah, yeah
Justin was sitting over there and this guy was checking me out from across the bar and Justin was like
Why is that guy staring at you? I'm like because he's hitting on me Justin and he's like no, why is he why does he keep staring at you?
So I like was like, all right, Justin. I got into the bathroom. So I went to the bathroom and like
He's on why you hate him? Sorry
Who's on?
People's podcast
Yeah, that's where she comes from and she over here over here stalking me like get out of here
Get out of here Katie said no, she did not she commented chat a new attack for her name is easy wifey. Oh, you who attacked her
Right. Yeah. Yeah, my wife never had a name like that. Somebody else came with fake name
I'm gonna I'm gonna make a
Easy wifey
Anybody can make it easy wifey page. What the fuck is wrong with you?
Oh
That's that's nasty. He was even laughing after I said, babe, that's you she goes. No, that's no enemy. Oh
It's his wife. He's a lucky woman anyway
So I went to the bathroom and I came back and I said to the man
can you look over at that boy over there and
He doesn't think I could pick up a guy like you and that you weren't staring at me across the bar
Would you give him a thumbs up if you're staring at me across the bar and he turned around to give him the cheese face and thumbs up him
And then gave me a hug and I left
It's pretty funny
Justin doesn't think that I can pick up 23 year old men at the bar
And I was
12 years younger maybe
I'm just saying a maybe I don't I don't discriminate on none. Don't trust me. It's always a maybe
Listen here if you got to know my personality you'd be down for whatever
Yeah
I think easy easy play cool play cool. I want buddy, but
That's my style. I like to play cool. That's why I was always a maybe
It's always a baby. Oh
My god, Gotti said boiled one day. I'll come home and see smokey with a G repair man
Well, keep sleeping on me, Justin, you see what happens.
Well, I want you to do, Justin, you got to get a job at.
Oh, Justin, she said, step the game up, not your funny up.
She said, step the game up, and shut the shut up.
No, Justin's good. I'm just messing with him. I just think it's funny that like he doesn't he doesn't believe me. Oh
He believes you he's just playing he's pretending he doesn't to test you
God he's got a head to tell him some shit. He still don't believe it
Yeah, oh
Let's see. I got good CB eraser. How's he rena? How's that? I saw you on betas
Spoky one day you'll come home and see Justin with the homeless uga that lives in the oh come on
Already where he lives now, so I'm used to it
Got it. No, the only person that likes that joke is Chris K. And well, they'd like to too, but
I don't know just laughing pretty hard
Um, yeah, he's he left in chat to Mexico still the World Cup. Oh, no
Comment of the month, huh? The Nelson months or something
Nelson was a sad person because he was really bully. That's why he was a bully
Don't drink
If you don't be if you drink for you drink if you drink for the Mexican World Cup make sure you like you know
Wash it first so you don't get Monizuma's revenge. Oh my god
Yeah, I
Don't know. It's a really bad diarrhea joke. It was running. It's running through my mind. It was really ready
He has to go to him spunky like he's gonna get mad at me and say stop talking to my girlfriend
I'm trying to like yeah, here he goes. He's gonna get nasty
It seems like he's like he's doing you're hitting on me and it's over and I can't talk to you anymore
Yeah, he's about to get mad spunky better go to him
I mean, it's because I'm vaping in the house and he's mad
Oh, okay. Oh, oh, I'm just shying in the house. Vape doesn't
I've got a vape on his sausage
I'm up. I already vape on his sausage and apparently it's over
What happened he broke up
Went down. Oh, yeah, well, you know that happened and now I can't vape in the house. So
Oh
Don't they too close
To his penis next up. Okay, there's just okay
What are you guys doing
Everything see that you're behind a wall. I can't see anything anymore. I just thought I'm using my imagination
My imagination is pretty dirty
You don't want to know what I'm going on right now
Now I remember what she what she meant easy wifey. I was fucking playing around with some girl on in that
Except I'm calling her wifey your wife a wife a and then she came through issues
I made the profile easy wifey for you. You won't use the other one. I
Remember what you're talking about easy next time you see me easy wifey prevails me
It could be anybody
That's me
Yeah, you might attack me in the chat you might attack me in the chat I want to get tackled in the chat
Always get attacked in the chat. Oh, please
Justin Boyle in the chat
right thing
That'd be
Is it easy to gangsta?
I'm even looking up the I'm even looking up the name right now like what the fuck this bitch talking about
What the fuck was easy right here if my wife did not have that name. Let me look up the name
Trying to find a person don't find shit
Wow, KZ, oh hi, hi KZ, hi Eraser, JT, Bickey, Rain.
I had to go vape in another room because I'm so offensive.
Okay.
Yeah, well people get mad at people smoking inside.
But you can't even smoke inside your car in California outside. You can't even walk down this in the pier
It's totally illegal to smoke. Oh my god. So normally I live about 25 minutes from
Justin's house 35 in the most
It took me two and a half hours and two different freeway shutdowns to get to his house tonight
Wow, it took a while. It was miserable
One was a car accident
and the other one was a man who decided at the
Dusk to go out and rescue a turtle from the freeway and
He got hit by a semi. Oh, no
Turtle I mean these turtles are causing so many problems. They're supposed to be so
The blessing if the cops shut down the whole fucking yeah, so Justin wants to know he's over here
Where you live if someone dies on the freeway do they shut down the entire freeway
Uh, they probably just try to shut down as like as many lanes probably try to leave one lane open
So it doesn't get like, you know backed up for hours because they can take a very long time
Well, they shut down this man who was saving this turtle was in the the exit lane
Four hours they did it
Well, crazy. I don't have time anymore without that. Okay. Come on. JC. Why are you being now? Stop attacking Hannah in the shed?
Okay, rain fatality, but when stop saying it's time for a wrench. I'll say hey, it's time for a wrench
Also, that's you. I
Don't know. They're trying to do my control on me. Maybe they'll be like, oh, here you go
And then it's in the rain at the same time
Look your favorite. Give me a wrench and make everyone mad. I won't even use it. I don't even know how
Thank you. I had a wrench earlier and I want to go block on rain
And the blocking huff on the panel itself. I'm like, no, I got on blocker now
Well, cuz I'm used to where the block buttons at the bottom
So you block somebody's at the bottom and when I went to a wrench is something different. So fuck
Hey guys
Guys we're working out all the kinks in the wrenches, okay, but it's almost it's almost there
Black like you can't block personal people when you got a wrench unless you don't got a wrench you block
Spunky posting the chat if you can you just did
She put I let my fail. I let my fail. I'm only face. I'm only face
There we go
It's it is fair JT. It's fair because now
No, spunky and in God he have them and I trust trust them most so oh my god, God he has a wrench
Yeah
Yeah, I got
Gotting I made a back room deal. I can't really tell you more than that
But I got I got a little nervous when I saw that said fuck. I'm gonna wait. Thank you
Can we pull a gaudy butthole card?
Well, this is to a regular guy. I mean, I don't want to just pull for buttholes. I mean, it's like, you know
This butthole in his life
Well, let's pretend we can say the butthole is like attached to the eventually the you know
The allegedly part of it, but but hold allegedly, you know, okay. Hold on. It's got even guy. I mean, are you in the chat?
It's in the chat we got
You got rain
We got boy, you got here. We got Jamie Cowboy
Which KT
Don't call her a witch. She knows she literally got here like a witch though straight straight and blonde. Okay, no straight and white. Oh
So God, you ready? So God, you have this card for you. Okay, this is God
You get a this can be it's gonna apply to your butthole. It can apply to your face
But whatever whatever you feel comfortable with your phone
The but okay, so whatever okay, so here here he says it says amidst the squirrel. Oh, it is the butthole. Okay, there's a swirl
There's a candle there's a can aloney he was eating the can aloney it was barely the digestive that there it goes
Okay, that's what's going into his world. That's what happened it right now
Yeah, it's a can aloney. It's a candle
It says steady, steady presence,
inner stability, navigating complexity,
centered awareness, grounding,
and amidst change, and trusting inner navigation.
God need to have these laughing.
Yeah, yeah.
I missed most of them.
Ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Luckily they're married. It's gonna be
Hey, she got even more rights now to throw something up in his ass
well
Let's leave that let's leave this sacred a couple stuff to the couple. Okay. I love your butthole
Got it. I don't love your butthole. It's you know, it stinks. Got it. It stinks. I think it stinks
Got it gets my job, okay
Okay. Okay. Okay. That's enough. That's enough. Okay. Who is spunky telling about my b-hole? Everybody
Gotti got Robert on the mind good cb. Oh, I guess who's here?
It's easy and spunky
She was always so nice.
She is.
Thank you.
It's like that sounded good. That was a good read. It was a good read on God. He's butthole, right? Yeah. Yeah
But for now on if you want me to read for the butthole because it's like
To free butthole readings in my life
And then the rest of them
are gonna be paid readings, okay?
And these $5, and I have to actually look
into your butthole and see what I see.
Oh, Lord. Oh, we're sick shows up for the butthole writing. They're sick.
He gave me the room and we're spending buttholes and then he like
What's good? He thought the fruit. He thought this was a freak off. He's like, oh hell, though.
Okay, so that's the first I was thinking about the back page. We go up a second. Oh,
shit. Yeah, gotta get Gotti and JT up here and rain.
Oh my god, guys, the speedo might be coming out tonight.
I don't know, we'll see what happens.
No, no, no, let's see, Vicky, the laugh is adorable.
Yes, oh, okay, cool, we got.
I don't know, BSVs, then my laugh is not adorable.
It's a turn off.
Well.
Sorry, that's a true genuine, wholehearted laugh.
I love authentic. Yeah, it's not in the laughs authentic. I hate a fake laugh or like a force lap or like I really like
I don't know some some laughs some funny sounding laughs are funny. Some are annoying. Okay. That's not your fault
My mom I don't know. There's a couple people lives in this platform that I'd be dying
I'd be like when they start laughing I'll be I'll be I'll be I'll start laughing off. I'm not online. I'm dying
Yeah
Like to laugh a lot. It's good for you
Or is Lenore
You know, I drive you nuts, you know that right?
I'm sorry. You saw her several times today, huh? Yeah. Did you see the white panther favorite?
You didn't know that don't tell the other ones. Yeah, don't tell
You look cute on your profile picture. Oh, thank you. I
Yeah
and and
Lenore tricks and don't tell Rudy cuz now all three
You in your profile picture
That's a real cutie right there. That's a flirt. Listen, baby. I ain't doing nothing, baby
No, no, I'm trying to get on now. No, you married. I got a man too. I'm happy to but you look cute
That's all I'm saying
Same here. Same here goes around. No comes around
That's all right
Yeah, he's cute a
Like some money for memberships and stuff
I didn't know how to do it on the phone and I thought oh, you know
We could just do it to the chat and then we could get golden girls trivia tarot. I got you
I got you Jamie. Just give it to the cash out. That's how I do it and let him buy membership. Oh
Well, that's what I did yesterday. I did it twice. I bought two of them if I believe right? I think and then I know
Yeah, I know you probably wanted to use it for like food and stuff and I'm like no no no no no
second
Yeah, Jamie's not a man. No
Even if it's backstage such a shit, I'll write what I want to do it for that
All this stuff. Yeah. Yeah
Say kick Alexander's or like for terror cards by terror
You know, yeah
Yeah, she has a vintage golden girls sec and she wants to come on a place soon so
When Barnes and Nobles was going out in California a long time ago a while back
I bought all the golden girls, you know set and then the purse of Sophia's so I will never open it. Oh
You buy Sophia's purse is like actual
Everything's in it site. I'll DM you but everything's in it and I'm golden butthole
Wow, that is the good as oh, how are you Jamie? You got fans out there my friend. Um, I know, you know member school
He said yeah, that was good. I mean the comedy. So it was good. Look
I know I know I like tell Jamie. I said was cooking good-looking. I
Would they ever call me a bitch today? No joke. I love that store. Sorry. I do too
I went there today, and I bought a shirt that I wore out to the bar tonight
You know, they had to pleasant him all over by San Francisco. So that's where it's at and open you
We were talking the other day Levi's are the best pants
my 16 year old son was like take me to the mall and I took him to one
He was like take me do another and I was like, what is this and then he was like after that
I want to go to Ikea and I'm like, okay. I'll take you there, too
It's Dingle here. No. Dingle's not here. How do we get Dingle here? Oh, what's wrong with Dingle?
Dingle's been giving my boyfriend good boy lessons.
Oh, I think Dingle got wiped.
How old are y'all? Have you mind?
Dingle settings is mid-thirties. Oh, he's in my mid-thirties right now. 35.
Oh my god, Gotti shut up tingles not in heaven get off his nuts
Your man is dingle the boy had a guy no no no
My boy is Justin Boyle that comes in here
Rain don't make it rain no accusations
In search of good boy lessons for my man oh shout out to be good
Dingle is amazing. I I'm gonna do a dingle when I when I bring up a Justin
Dingles the man
Justin better look just to give you the side out right now
He's not in the room, but but I'm telling him
The next boy on my card. Oh shit schools here. I was I'll be in the chat. I'll be in the chat. Just like that
school, what up?
Hey, buddy. Hey, what's up?
School. Hey school. Hello. Hello. Hello. I'm just getting um Broly. I want to go and show you a little bit of Broly, my cat
Herbie's in the chat
Psyche knows Psyche knows Broly. Yeah, I saw Broly. I saw Broly on summers
You did?
You showed Broly already
Yeah, I don't know of Jamie's if Jamie girl, so
I
Jamie driver see Broly
Is that the brown one site the brown one cat that he had on the video? No
My cat's a Neva masquerade if you know what that is
Like white and gray with the blue eyes and the lion man off the main I have a main cone and a calico
Oh, you have a main cool. That's what we're deciding that we're gonna get an Eva masquerade or a main codes are the best
Background earlier Leo come here. Oh
You know his things Leo right? Yeah. Yeah, Leonardo the caprio. We were talking about that
I had a Romeo that was my main cool and because he had a heart on his side in his fur, but
Boy got taken out by three
Oh my god, I'm drunk. I can't remember.
He's so funny.
Not Pitbulls, but...
Oh, god.
Rottweiler?
Rottweiler.
Rottweilers.
They were three Rottweilers, exactly.
That's what he got to go by.
He lived through the attack from three Rottweilers, and I called Animal Control and the three
Rottweilers, which were not put down.
They were just taken back, which ended up taking out a person.
Which was crazy, but uh, he yeah, he did good poor boy. No
Yeah, I'll put some pictures of him up on the
Yeah, you know, that's my boy right there. That's my boy right there. I did not
Look, I put a picture of my dog psyche
That's my boy that's Tyler
Yeah, shout out to for you know losing jack
He was laid up
What the less of us are so good?
Hmm. I'm sorry
That's really
I'm sorry. Oh, here's a good close one. Yeah, that's it. I'm sorry, buddy. I heard what you were saying
It's really said I
Had another calico, but I had to put her down last year
Oh, I didn't put it down. I just I'm just not with him right now. Me. I did. Oh my god. I got my cousin's dog right now with me
My name was shot. Oh
Psych knows Psych knows Callie. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I remember that
Yeah, that's the one. Oh
Yeah
It's crew I'm out to do something like that too money. I like how you I mean money
Oh, I like how you represent it. Oh, yeah, everybody is trying to get up here and stop playing around
I know you're done with your sponge bath. Yeah, really
It's a sponge bath. That means not we're done. Jamie is waiting for you to get up here. He's cool
She's never up here. She's waiting for you to come up. I've been up here a couple times
A couple times. Yeah
Yes, well, because Jamie's been with the show since probably like September or October last year when I started doing the live streams
Yeah, we started it. She's been from the beginning, right?
Yeah
You're still waiting for you
They started up as a pirate right
See him when he stretched out like the man koon. Yeah. Oh, that's the cat. That's the cat. Yeah, it's like you put it up there real quick
Yeah, they do and we got him little pantalones you see how he's shaved because he loves being shaved and then little pantalones on the
He's smart as hell too
They're real smart. Yeah, the Neva masquerades are the
Veterinarians said we should put them on a leash. They're one of the few cat breeds that
You can train them with the leash. They like it because most cats don't and
Now we could take them off the leash and he just walks around right next to us like a dog. Yeah, they're real smart
I have a
Siamese now and then I just a mixed breed cat and they're stupid as shit
that's what he's half believe it or not he's half Siamese because this goes
back like 2,000 years it's Russian so half Chinese and half Siberian you know
the Siberian cats so that's what they are half and half that's what an even
masquerade is but they're hunters you know
I feel so bad. I want to wake him up, but he's sleeping so sound right here
I want to kill what I like push his head, but he's sleeping so sound. I got a mute second yellow. Justin. I'll be right back
Okay
How you do it's like you look like you're on point again. It's nice to see
Okay, no good. Yeah
You don't play that bull. Yeah, he's on point. He's on point. He's on point
of all things
Yeah, I'm good. I'm good. I'm
good. Yeah. Yeah. I'm good.
I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
I'm good. I'm good.
And then fireworks went up and boomed
Yeah, that's it
Now I have a video, I have a video
I, but hey listen
I always cover my ass
I'm smart guy, I have a video of it
You're a robot and buddy
What'd you say?
It might be my wifi
No, I have a video of it though
So I can
Does anyone know what he said
That he has a video of?
I don't, I can't
Fireworks
No, what happened was I said a little fireworks earlier and you said the burden of proofs on you trying to be funny
And I was being funny and so I had a video
You were talking so fast I was talking about have a how have you been but I was just joking with the burden of proof
But now I get what you did there. I like that. That was good now. It's joking to you
Yeah, that was good. I like this because you know what this ghost sounds like he's on point, too
that
You just hit that fucking wall, and it was like free for all time, you know what I mean? It's like everything changed.
I did have one thing to say, and I'm not trying to argue anything. I want to talk to that. I'm going to call them all. Allergy, whatever his name is. Allergy.
Allergy?
What allegedly are you talking about? He's in the oh, oh and the top right no because when I'm looking at because I have you on my phone
But I have you on my TV, but it's all it's stuck on one picture where I don't like and that I'll tell you that picture
You got a change that you look like I shake a fish
Wow
That's like the picture that I'm seeing it's him with his tie on and with his hat on and yeah, it's these that's these
You don't know who that is. So no I
JJ fish
That's easy.
Easy camera's on.
Yeah, I'm not sure
Well, how about this golden girls, let's get back to the golden girls
My favorite golden girls episode because I love the golden girls. I love the golden girls. Yeah
Oh, I love them so much is the Quentin Tarantino episode. Do you remember the Quentin Tarantino episode? Mm-hmm
Do you I do a little bit of it
You was when he dressed up as Elvis you remember when they had all the Elvis's yeah, and she forgot to cancel
That's my favorite one, but I love golden girls trivia on hallmark or if you switch over it's on the other channel. So yeah, I
Just have it all on DVD still like every episode my grandmother gave it to me before she passed
All right, let's do a little trivia in what city did the Golden Girls live?
Oh, excellent. What county?
Hey, was a day County very good
I'm gonna keep track here to one for sight. I don't watch this shit. I got you
One for ghosty. All right ready. What was Blanche's cook making in the opening scene of the pilot episode?
Cheesecake
All right, I'll give you a multiple choice was it huevos rancheros
Was it a Spanish omelet or was it enchiladas rancheros be?
Nope, you got it. See see. Yeah, you got it. You got it. You got it's like he
He was only a one episode, right?
Yes, you're right. Actually, you're right. It was a link in the beginning of the series. Where did rose work?
Titanic oh, yeah, Jack very much. What did she do?
He worked at like a news station
No, but there's no more
I'll give you yeah, right. I'll give you the three things at a diner
Counseling Center or an animal hospital Counseling Center. That's right. That's right. That's why they call her a midnight
That's right. That's right. Do you want me to keep going or should I stop is this boring?
I'd rather you pull a fucking cart. What is the name?
This is a good one. What is the name?
Of the man who proposes to Blanche in the pilot episode the first one because they're afraid like she's gonna leave or whatever
Mm-hmm. I forgot that one
Harry Joe Bob or Don Harry Harry. That's right. That's right on that on the plane. You're good. That's holy shit
I to be honest with you. I didn't know that I just looked that up. I
Yeah, you're totally right with the meat coat
God damn, you're not looking that up, huh? No, I'm a huge fan. I'm not sure just I know me too. I love the golden girls
Oh, hey, please Rusty you're being very dramatic
This is my this is my job. Well, Rusty says I guess this is Hannah's channel now
They're kind of fighting the
You see it says
There's Hannah rest either rusty who is rusty is platform boots says I guess this is Hannah's channel now
Or Trana she held the channel
You see where it says owner that means I am my channel. Okay, I
Don't know what's going on. Yeah, you better recognize. I was reading the chat
Okay, oh my god. Okay. Now the email is coming guys. Let's all calm down. Okay. Let's go. Let's go on
Now you should have called it out. That's good job
What's the answer? This is good stuff. Yeah, you read in the chat Justin says, uh, what president I know that one
That's there Reagan Reagan Reagan. No, it's Herbert Walker Herbert. Oh Jimmy Carter. Oh Jimmy Carter. No, it was it was
GHW be George Herbert Walker
Right Justin Anna you say dumb dumb. You don't say that word
Don't know Justin still I think it's Jimmy Carter, but maybe I know for a fact. I remember it was George HW Bush
Okay, I guess it was George, but okay. Hmm. Yes. It was joy. Yeah, we got Justin. Good question
You got any more Justin the first or the second look at his psyche as for the first the first
Yeah, it's Herbert Walker. That's
Right new cards
Oh, yeah, I do cards George. Would you like a card go take a card a ghost and a
Ghost and how near Liz it's Athens. It's just one card. It's a brand. It's brand new. I just got it today
It's opened it. Yeah, it's called
Okay, that's what I got you. Okay
Okay, but your card is
Okay, your card ghost is called
My goodness, this would have been a good but card ghost this might apply to your butt to hold on
Because remember where like oh
We're reading for the butts. Okay. Hold on. So you got this you you got the cheeky challenge
You got the cheeky challenge and there's Mario. Okay there that look like you go settle
Ah, I kind of take your picture a little bit. She got the cheeky challenge
right and it says
Playful confidence, lighthearted defiance, owning presence, self-assuredness, style and
sass, challenging norms and authenticity.
It says, when the world, meet the world with a wink and a dream, your playful prayer is
Okay, so no matter if you're going through a lot of shit like he's like, ah, but he's so
So it's good when he's doing it. He's Mario fuck it. You know Mario, right? Okay, so that was for ghosts. You'd like that ghost
Well, thank you
And for Athens wait, thank you. Can I shoot question before you pull it?
Okay, I'll be is that a like a Nintendo deck? No, this is no this is his different art
It's like a lot of a lot of different pop culture art and it's just me with me as an Oracle deck
But that was like Mario in there like that's like a trademark. What's like the name of the deck?
This is called the inner worlds
Oracle card. I think it's more it's more of a pair. I think that's a parody of Mario
It kind of is not okay. I'll I'll take one. I'll take one. Okay. Okay. Okay, seventh card psyche
Seven you're thinking you're the seventh card. Okay. Yeah, seventh card seven. Yeah. Yeah, what's the seventh card?
For eight for infinity
Okay, your card is interduality, okay, and it's
It says light and shadow, integration, duality, acceptance, wholeness, conflicting aspects, authentic power, and self-awareness.
And it says, true wholeness arises not from choosing sides, but from courageously embracing the vibrant dance of opposites within.
There you go. And I think that's really good. I like that self-awareness. That's good
Yeah, and it reminds me of a little bit of your your omnisum your omnisum where it's like it's got a lot of like everything is there
conflicting
That's like a finish ghost. No, it's all but it's all integrate you integrate it and you you make it all
Balance within yourself. We'll put the both sides of the duality. So you're okay
Help them
Yeah, I've got a phone call. I'll kick off. Okay. Thank you, psyche
That's Leo. Sorry. Thank you. We'll read it again, right? I didn't understand minds early. I was like really out of it
Okay. Yeah, you're a little bit
I'll pull you another card
Don't they have the
Infinite 8
That's gonna be a new one. You gotta pull him
This is the one that he got
I'm gonna reshuffle
Number 8
Are you gonna fuck it all up now?
You're not the person they're giving a read
You don't know what needs to be heard
I believe you know me. Oh, that's why we over here. Why you didn't under that's why you didn't understand it earlier
It's like I had so I was out of it. I vote just woke up understand the situation
Okay, so here's the user is easy if this has peep
So we're gonna ask the deck down there stand it. It says peace serenity peace serenity
But then it's like oh look at that one. He's like, I mean serenity, but it's like maybe wow
It's like
It says, inner peace, serenity, high perspective, calm observation, clarity, stillness, emotional
altitude, inner growth, and intuitive guidance says, from the quiet peak within, bathed in
serene light, the vast landscape of self unfolds in perfect peace.
Everything's I'm fully of the shit. Oh, okay. Okay, JT
JT, I like where Justin's going with the Mortal Kombat
Yeah, mm-hmm. I like it over here was my favorite
He was my favorite in the first one and then in the second one. I liked reptile
Oh, that was the big two
Mortal Kombat Luke. I like reptile
My favorite character to the whole series to the whole series my favorite character. It's the guy Johnny cage
Johnny guy that pops up in the corner and goes
Yeah, yeah, that was because of Scorpion though, right like that was like the that's um Ed Boone
Do you know who that is Ed Boone? I don't care who was that? He was the creator of all the way I'm back
Ed Boone we're all shitting on Lord Raiden
Yeah, he's soft, dog.
Raiden's soft.
He's the one who landed her back in the 90s.
The best guy was Noob Saibot.
Noob Saibot.
Yeah, there you go, brother.
You remember him?
There you go.
Yes, I do.
Yeah, that's the...
Do you know how they got that name?
Smoke was the shoot idea idea, but it's fucking it's it's the name backwards noob is boon
Yeah, and Saibot is Tobias because that's the two creators backwards like their names backwards boon and not Tobias
Imagine they put a Mike Tyson in there
Yo, they try you know what they tried to do they asked John Claude Van Damme
that he was he was too close to Johnny Cage, though
Yeah, but he was supposed to
Yeah, but it was supposed to be John Claude Van Damme
It wasn't supposed to be Johnny Cage and like he turned it down and all that, you know
And they turned it into Johnny
When he's died of his career and everything there
Rain is official too boy
Wish yeah, Spongebob, you tell him Rain is official too
Purple rain crazy was the early 90s, man. I think he's the one with the acid, right?
Did the girl freak you out like especially in that first movie like or it might have been the second one before oh
Yeah
I'm with you. Yeah, I'm with you. He did kind of freak me out
That's when I got like I was like all women are so badass because
Sonya cage remember she looked Kato's ass to do with the red eye. No Sonya blade
I don't know which one is the original now. I can't tell me the real. Oh
And then the other two were Katana and Malina, Malina.
I heard girls saying the real ghost no more. There's a new ghost in town. No, there's a new one in the original is the best.
I don't know which one is the original now. I can't tell me the real.
Wait Jamie, what are you talking about?
the the Mortal Kombat
We did it in this 90s was the best one. I think oh, I see what you're saying. Yeah, they came out with like a
So there's two. There's actually three right they had the original the sequel in the 90s and then they have
Yeah, but all those bullshit series you're saying Jamie the new major major motion picture full length, right? Oh, yeah
Um, you can watch they got movies on that shit like they took out the game fight and they made a movie out of it
Are you two the notions it's fucking official?
Yeah, but they're all right, but like the new movie. I'm still with Jamie
The original is the best
He's actually a real samurai in real life. He's a badass in real life. You play a lot of movies
Uh, the scorpion guy that played in the new movie. He's actually a fucking badass
I forget his name. Yeah, but I'm still a Jamie original mortal
Had the soundtrack your
soundtrack I want to put on that shit right your brother soul is mine. Yeah
Tasha so good
original. I'm going to look
for it right now. original. It's
like, go over here. Yeah.
Everyone knows that. Even if
you're not a fan. And you know
people are dancing at the club
up to that shit. Hell yeah,
they were, but I want to say
this. Man, they were like,
get down. Oh, yeah. I remember
the difference. Our King
Yeah, but this is what I was just gonna say to you. I'm 43 right so I went away on vacation snowboarding in
1995 that's when Mortal Kombat 2 the arcade game and you would go up there and you'd wait and you'd put your quarter up on
There because the winner would stay on and if you lost and you called the winner trash or like yo
You suck you're gonna get smacked in the mouth
You know nowadays because all this online with the headsets
People just call each other all these names and shit and they don't like nothing happens to them
Then when they get older and their adults, they don't they still like have that mindset
Do you know what I mean Jamie is like and then that's what had that's why there's so many problems and crazy shit going on because
They're not used to it, but consequences.
Yeah, because if you're friends with someone,
you can say shit to them like...
It wasn't this thing online.
It was a side-by-side...
Big, big, big, big, big, big...
People talk to each other different than...
Exactly, ghost.
That's right, ghost.
Because there's no consequences, right, ghost?
Right.
There were consequences back then.
But they're being friendly, too.
They're not even being disrespectful to each other.
But bro if you watch and you son of a bitch, bro, think about it
Do you want online game at all? Do you like play anything online like any online gaming? Like modern?
Well, yeah, I do
So it's like I play PUBG right like PUBG and shit, and you play Call of Duty
I heard you say modern warfare. How many times do you hear something?
But how many how many times do you know?
Oh, we do the monster front group every fucking day.
I mean, every minute, like, especially a month's loss.
But if somebody else says it like, yeah,
we'll have an argument, never take any of that shit serious.
Like, we're just on the ground.
Yeah, but then, when they go out driving in their car,
we just talk shit.
Yeah, but think about this.
When they go out driving in their car
and they get like cut off or something,
that whole gaming thing where they can call somebody trash
or put somebody down and not have consequences,
that will kick in.
And they'll place put their hand out the window fuck you, US or and then that personal fucking like maybe do something
now
Call the duties and a lot of games got
Band systems where you your name will get banned just like
um, something from youtube
So I know I play xbox
Like you don't
I was playing Call of Duty a couple months ago, and I was talking shit. Oh, you motherfucking
We're going to him and next you know
I was banned for a week. I couldn't play the game. I couldn't put people. Let me ask your question
He's were you banned for a day like before that because I got banned for a day one time because a kid
Lied and said I was being racist and all this shit and
Gotty, I just almost died come on panel. Oh
Yo
We're not good at boom
What happened here beer was too big
Yo, shout out to my boy allegedly psych school. Oh my god. Is that shorty? Is that shorty?
Yo
How you doing my boy just got to the crib bro chillin better. Are you doing my boy? I'll take it
I like when easy says that. How you doing my boy?
What happened Alexander, you know, he's low-key watching right now, you know, he is bro
Some crazy I want him to come back though, bro, I don't know whatever you guys got going on
You know, no, I got to respect you though Sean because you were laughing and you heard me get a little tight
You know the other night
And I was like, yo, you keep laughing and he's going to keep talking and then you went, everybody went silent and he didn't know what to do. You know what I mean?
Yeah, bro. So I respect you.
I didn't want to instigate. I was like, yo, let me mind my business.
Yeah.
It's like a touchy thing for both.
Whatever they got going on. I'm like make it in my business. You know, Alexander
He's got something going on with everybody everywhere, you know, free Alex though free
I have free Alex, but I seen you in the chat too. Yo, you were like Alex STF you I seen you write that so respect to you
You know, yeah, some things, you know, it's like got to keep
Everyone
Like psyche knows that bullshit fuck Alex we got sick
Call him a queen don't call it don't speak about the devil the devil gonna pop up, right?
He's like a Alex yeah, yeah, it's dragging them in right now his fingers is
Is heavily is twitching above the link it's itching
It's an unfortunate he glitched
He bought a catchable he's gonna be rich and what's your deal? What's up? I'll treat you like
I think and I are both on the edge of death. So we just hang in there. We're saying what's up. Yes, it was good man
Yo, you're muted, buddy. Yeah, I think he's Mike's on low
What happened
You're good I'm doing good. I've been worried about you. I'm sorry to hear that you're worried about me
I'm doing well. No, like not like in a bad way. I just been like what's up with sick? That's all
Ah, enough with that soft ass shit, man, hold on, hold on, fucks it.
Never mind, let me go back. Fuck's sake, you sick of me dad, I don't know shit.
Yo, let's get back to the fight. Yo, Jamie girl, do you know that Shawn B is gonna fight at Madison Square Garden?
She's the freakiest one I met, she's crazy, funky.
Yo, did you know that, Jamie?
I was hearing about it, yeah, our friends were talking about it.
Yeah, Shawn, when is it? Did you get any more info? What's the deal?
Bro, I got the info easy here right now. I
Like you know same shit. I said that the whole doxing thing. So I'm just what are you drawing till it's mad close
Um, and that's it bro that I'm how far away though. Are we talking two weeks?
Like two two and a half weeks a little on there and we're getting excited me and for me and I'm gonna pull up
I'm stopping camp
Officially like three to four days before you know, so my body could like little recover a rest
You know reset and not too much
When am I gonna know what day though cuz I'm gonna pick I told you I'm going to
Money's house on Thursday. I'm gonna I'm gonna get you and fall in the private ship because I already got for everybody
I got easy
School Christine
I'm gonna be there though with money because I'm selling my ticket. I'm selling my ticket right now. I'm selling my ticket
For how much I can't wait showing I can't wait bro. It's already 57 for how much you're selling it bro
I can't wait
150 I'm selling it for a buck like come on bro. I can't wait. You're gonna kill this guy, bro
I'm winning by points with decision
Yeah, knock them out that's TOS. That's TOS saying you're gonna do what to somebody
Fighting at the garden fighting a medicine square garden in a boxing match. That's TOS
Madness get squatted a bit
Mm-hmm. Shout out to signal. I don't know what happened, but he lost signal
No, I think he does
This is for real, bro. It's not it's for real
It's a real fight. It's a real fight. He's on the undercard and to anybody that um, bro
He's in the cards already the fire because I did see it's already set up some people that ask, you know
Change sides and down. I can't wait. Not true school though
You want to eat you always, you know, and niggas always have faith in me
Hell yeah, bro. Yo, I can't wait. Me and money gonna pull up
And we write yo cuz all we're gonna do is is I'm not even gonna drive there
I'm driving to money's house, and I'm gonna park my car there and him and I are gonna take the yeah
And I'm gonna take the subway to the garden
I mean after whatever niggas could go get eats all it up, bro
Oh, that's what we're gonna chill. Yeah, cuz I'm going to uh money's house on Thursday this week this Thursday
And I'm bringing them three computers
We're gonna hook them up again and then and then hopefully we know a little more info, you know
But we're gonna talk about it that night. I'm psyched bro. Yo, I'm psyched. No, bro
I'm yesterday, you know, I was like, you know, cause I said back after I'm like, yo, let me think about the conversations we had, bro, it's a little bit sad, you know, like Alex to my niggas like same thing with the damn like niggas, niggas down to me for me.
So it's like, I'mma put on bra told you, bro, I'm not going out like no sucker, bro.
But you remember Alex, you remember Alex last week, Sean Alex was the good Alex, you remember before he turned into McQueen.
He was telling you to remember he was being all positive with you. That's what you got to remember
We were saying I don't fuck with that two-faced shit like it's like bro if you well
He just gets all crazy, you know him
I like easy easy said the rail and remember easy like you'd be on the rails. That shit was great
For me shit bro, I got mad shit going on in the cut too, bro like
Like, you know, it was so funny
School 4th of July though, I got to like chill, you know, I'm saying like do my own thing
Like get away from the gym and all the bullshit, you know, and I thought I was got to chill
But I went to Coney 4th of July got there late like not 30, but I was there mad late though fire was from crazy
Pat
Got a little snack out there chill smoked
They had an event in Harlem tool for the kids and shit
They had breakfast on all that basketball training. Yeah, we know you ain't gonna stop talking about
Boxing unless we reel you in but all I know is Sean. You're you're my boxing guy
I lost money last night. Yo, did you did you see the soccer match? You know, did you watch the USA Mexico?
Oh, I didn't even know today. I see Mexico. It was the gold cup
Shout out to the the gold cup. Yeah, we lost though two to one for me school
It's bigger than just a boxing. You know, this is like a what means maybe a way out
To get out to do something better in life escape the rat race in New York or even worry about
Did you watch the Golden Girls ever the Golden Globes no the Golden Girls
I love Jamie girls. I'm like you got a great laugh. Jamie you are so chill
What I like about Jamie is she she like if somebody does something for her or like
She remembers that and then she pays it forward because like you came in that other chat
You're like, yo, thank you and I didn't even know what you were saying at first and then you like made sure I knew what you were talking about
Bad video about me and that crushed me and I know it up for me. So thank you
I did. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Cause they were going. We were once friends, you know, it's sad, but I'm not going to go any further than that. Yeah. Yeah. We don't have to. But all's I was trying to say is being positive is when you like pay it forward, that makes me, you know, pay it forward to someone else too. And I try not you're, you're a positive existence. Do you know what I mean? Yeah. The ripples off of you positive. And I like that a lot of people in the show to be like, Oh.
One dollar will pay it forward, pay it forward.
Two dollars will pay it forward, pay it forward.
Three dollars will pay it forward to school.
On that week right now, I just looked that shit up.
Back here, are you on here?
Bunking I'm sorry about your dog much prayers. Okay. Yeah, I mean it really sucks
But like why is this bitch making fun of me for my dog dying like
Like who the fuck is she
Those are you those are kids right there you spend like 15 to 20 years
Those are your fucking family
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
After that though, what's the thing that you did after it's like you come back?
Wait, that's who Alex was talking about who does that I like to talk about everyone who didn't know
In the chat being a bitch to me about my dog dying and I ain't having it
Yeah, come on. There's like that's probably Alex. It's probably Alex. No this bitch
I've been on my nuts for a while and
Because I have the same dog on my channel. That's the same dog that should have died
God that's so negative. Did she come did she come up? I don't know Hannah. Did she come up?
I'm gonna get up. I'm gonna fucking come up here. I'd love to face her. Yeah, come up. Tell me about that. Hannah come on up
Come on up Hannah. You probably Alex
Do you know Hannah or no, is this the first time? No, I don't know Hannah. Hannah's just talking shit on me in chat
Come on up here, but I'm gonna burdo her ass
Why do I need to face? I'm not reading her perc. I got it cool. Oh, you're definitely
I'm like the nicest one in the fucking chat. That's Alex, but I'm psychotic
But yeah, bitch
I am psychotic when you want to fuck with me and talking about my fucking dog
Yeah, and I'm not dying like I'll fuck you up
And you know what and you know what Jamie when she's I'll tell you she's always positive and
school what are you talking about here's what i'm talking about how i'm talking about
about my babies and one of my babies died and you want to make fun of me for my babies
dying i'm gonna fuck your ass
Uh, come on up here, bitch.
I understand, I understand where you come from.
Sean, I don't know what you mean.
I didn't even finish what I was doing.
I'm sorry, babe, I'm sorry, I'm just a little heated.
No, not you.
I was talking to Sean.
I didn't know what to tell you.
No, I'm not.
Because she was like, man, serious.
She was about to fuck a bitch up and then...
Yeah, but I was trying to back her up.
I was trying to explain that she's positive all the time and it's like a teacher who yells
all the time.
You don't take them seriously.
She doesn't yell all the time.
It's like, yo, holy shit.
Do you understand what you want?
Yeah.
I mean, so if you want to get someone triggered, Hannah,
you got someone trigger, come on up here, bitch.
Come face your master.
Oh, shit.
We're going to learn a bitch today.
We're going to play learnabitch.com right now.
Let's go.
Get on up here.
Damn.
I'll sign up for it.
Yo, shut up, ghost.
Niggaz ain't trying to hear that bullshit right now.
Ghost, we ain't playing with you right now.
I don't know, Jamie.
What's going on here?
I'm letting her handle it like she should maybe I'm sorry. I know I know don't be sorry. You know, I know bugger
I know sorry. You got a hold of that. Well, you need to hold it down girl. Yeah, that's right
Hey, you know Eldon asked me about that video and everyone knew of you know, here we go
And I told Athens you want the truth here. It is just ask me. I love Jamie's accent from
It is it's so chill
We'd be talking terrible, right? He's right next to me
Here we go
Hey, there easy there was Hannah a man that was second
Yeah, I'm not Hannah. I
Know you're not and I know who you are
But there was Hannah was up on the screen for a second
I don't see her I don't see her I saw somebody come on I got a flabbergasted I fucking fat fingered the phone. I saw Hannah I thought you had to argue my girl.
Yo ghost play the bottom right corner ghost. Hey big baby. What's going on Amanda?
Nothing nothing nothing at all brother
Spongebob is that your picture there? Is that you? Yeah, honey. That's me. That's cool. I like your hair. Thanks
Nice. I was on here earlier on live. I I picked up some subscribers. I'm psyche from the bar
Now he doesn't does your boyfriend now yo school you know what is giving me that the blonde the short hair
Like you know I'm saying that boss boss queen that coming like dressed up, you know casual, but sexy
You know I'm saying business. Maybe a little like that Russia
Bob's you know I'm saying like that business Polish baby. I'm Polish all right Eastern Eastern European though
That's what I was going at
That's a Polish bitch right there single fuck you up
Yeah, I was asking if your boyfriend actually chatted with us. Yeah, he doesn't boil his name Jamie
Justin boils your boyfriend
My boyfriend
Well, he has good questions before the Golden Girls trivia
I don't know what the fuck he said. I was battling with a low blood sugar because I'm a type one diabetic
So I didn't see that and then I heard I was getting attached in the chat
And then I came back to life and I came back with a vengeance. Okay shit man free Poland free sponky
What that means
Yeah, it's yaks amash yaks amash yaks amash
And Yak Shamash Yak Shamash.
Oh my gosh.
He's screaming and telling you that I'm 2% Mongolian.
Oh, all right.
Mongol's a badass.
You're a Mongolian too.
Yeah.
I'm 2% Mongolian.
If you zoom in on my eyeballs, I have the eye slits like an Asian.
That's me.
Zoom in on my eyeballs.
That's the most beautiful people in the world.
You know that hat here?
Zoom in, motherfucker.
Zoom in.
Can you see it?
It's not really beautiful.
Hold on.
Let's go.
Zoom in right now.
Can you see the eye slits?
It's like an Asian.
She got the Turkish look.
Yeah, you got the Turkish look.
I'm zooming in right now.
I got screen shots.
Fuck the zoom in.
No, no, no.
Where's your car job?
She got the.
She got the lips I got the fucking green Irish eyes. Yeah, I got the Polish ass cheeks. Are those your lashes?
It's your rations in that picture.
She got a little two person. They ain't those, they ain't pure asses. They belong to my horse.
No, no, those are Turkish people are the most beautiful people in the world.
Dude, any other day, any other day of the week I'm wearing face lashes.
You look Turkish do a little bit. Oh, I'm not Turkish at all
I'm Irish Polish and a little bit Mongolian
You know, we're all a little Mongolian
Genghis Khan Genghis Khan had like, you know, I had a babushka
She's the fuck she taught me how to fucking make progies
Brogies are good. Yeah
I have a sweet
I do like the tatted eyebrows somebody said the tatted eyebrow. I do like that. Yo, I had a girlfriend
Because my immune system ain't all my eyebrows
Please
My ass has no cellulite, but my my forehead ain't got no eyebrows. I'll tell you that you want to know a sad story
I had a girlfriend for five years Polish and
Her grandmother like the not her grandmother, but her grandmother's sister was in Auschwitz and the Germans
pulled out her reproductive organs so she could not yeah that's a true story that was yeah that was
her grandmother's sister and she was just i'm just trying to talk real talk for like how lucky
we are and the juice plugged on my fallopian tube stuff just and then we're gonna have kids we're
gonna have to go to Mexico so there you go oh well the juice killed Kennedy as well i mean we can go
And I have
So I ain't come trying to say hey to you. I hope you didn't go to sleep
Nah, he's chillin. He's chillin right now
She playing the cut like a band-aid
About a roll up a squiff right now
Let's get a control
We don't hear you rolling
So Hannah doesn't want to play the game.
Come on, damn, damn, fuck all that drama shit.
A moment of silence, please.
Can we get a moment of silence, please?
This shit, you gonna get, you gonna get, uh, what's her name?
Sponky about to get back starter? She was about to kill Hannah.
Hannah already does. She already party done for her, but it's like...
It's all too much.
She writing paragraphs you see I can't do that man. We're not reading that bro. Yo, Jamie
Jamie did you watch the Abercrombie and Fitzgerald documentary on Netflix? No, I gotta go watch that
Oh my god, you got to watch it and see what happened the story about that company what happened in the
Back but it didn't stop me from buying their clothes. No, I said you see the did you see the shirt that I put up before no
Yeah, I'll put it back up again. I've had this shirt for like 25 years away from where school from where you could see my avatar
Look at my avatar. What does it say? Oh
I've had that shirt for 25 years.
At Agricrom, be sure this is trails.
You know that one that they came out with?
And on the back is all the different trails.
Yeah.
Because that's how it started.
It started in 1892 as a hiking company.
Hiking.
Yep, you're absolutely right.
That's very popular down by San Francisco here. Well by us in the mall
They had the three stores. They had a fish and then they had Hollister and then they had yeah
And then they had gilly Hicks. Do you remember that one? Yeah, and then they have and then they have a
Agri-Cromby across the way in Pleasanton
We don't have it anymore by us, but do you have you ever been in a gilly Hicks store? That's a undo that was ever crummy's underwear store
Oh my god
Crazy type of
How do I say this of?
Advertising you walk in and they build these tiny hallways and in you go down the hallway
And it's black and then they have the mannequin that just has like a sexy body on it with like a light on it in front of you
And then you like make a right and then there's another one and another one's very scary shit
Yeah
Yo, let's type it in on YouTube. Just type in YouTube like Gilly Hicks store 2000, you know, and you could see how they did
It's crazy. Yo school. What malls they got by your stores where they got like some crazy shit
Like what's the drip look I'm like for the summertime my smith even more and the Roosevelt Field Mall are the two big malls on Long Island
Yeah, Roosevelt
Roosevelt's in Nassau
Because I know there's QCM and Queens
See the reason why I said pleasant 10. I'm sorry keep kidding everybody's all
But pleasant 10s right before you get to San Francisco. So it's right out of you know, the way to go there Oakland
That's cool. And then has anyone ever been to Minnesota to that Mall of America?
Yes, yes, that's that's exactly that's exactly right. They're so big that mall that they sponsor the Minnesota Vikings Stadium. That's what the Minnesota. Yeah, it's called the Mall of America Stadium.
They have a water park in there too.
That's crazy.
The big one by me. I went to college in Cortland
It's upstate New York and then a little bit farther north is Syracuse. You ever heard of Syracuse?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, the college they have the carousel mall and that's a pretty neat
Yeah, that's like they have a like the carousel with the horses like a really big one in the middle
Yep, I'm listening buddy. What's up, bro? I need you to take me to a store to pick up
Pick a boy man weed. I just realized you have a car
You just realized it
You've known me for yeah, I gotta you know me
No, I know I know you'd be driving for work for like the you know
Delivering and taking up and helping customers like with the witcher personal car and shit
But I just remembered right now because I'm like hold on I think the school got a car right here, bro
And I asked what's his name?
I think it was Jay Famo. Whatever the fuck his name is he'd be up here
For god, but he's out here too. They're gonna be on the school and shit. I'm like yo come pick me up
He's a girl tolls congestion fees this day. I'm like guys
So yes, cool. We're gonna have you moving like the cartel, but we're gonna pick up some packs
You muted my boy, I'm sorry. I said do you want to hang out on Thursday?
Bro, yeah, I'm outside every day, my boy.
Well, on Thursday, I'm going to Money's House in Brooklyn.
Who, Money 420?
Yes, I told you this before
This channel
I'm going to start talking and chat the moment I fall off panel saying that I my dog died and
Then the same dog was up on panel. No, that wasn't the same dog. You dumb bitch
You're dumb son of a little fucking baby Pomeranian dog died
And I fucking miss him very much and you're a stupid fucking bitch for claiming that you know what the fuck is up
And you want to run your mouth in the chat the moment my fucking face is off panel
Come on up here
Let her do her thing what's up Katrina that's my musical guru
who's probably some fucking bitch like Jarl,
who can't come up here and show who she really is,
doesn't wanna come up and fucking say a thing,
but she just wants to run her mouth and chat.
But fuck you, bitch, my dog did die.
That does suck.
It really does fucking suck.
And you wanna be a bitch and rub dirt in my wound?
Over it?
Fuck you, I don't know who the fuck you are,
but you can fucking die in a fire for all the fuck I care.
I hope karma gets you like a mother fucker, stupid ass bitch.
Sorry.
That's all I wanted to say.
You girl, you girl is funky. Talk to your shit.
Yeah, you keep going. Don't be sorry. Listen, we, you know, we've all been blabbering the three of us.
Yeah, the fucking moment I get, my fucking phone dies, I had my iPad on, and then I see her talking shit.
The moment my fucking face falls off the panel, like you stupid whore.
You're showing picture avatar. I hate when those white things it is. That's just me. Sorry. I'll try. Yeah, I couldn't
Try to upload a picture and the shit don't crop bro like you don't take the picture
Do you have a good you have a phone? Do you have a phone? Yeah, I only got one device, bro
Yes, so all you got to do is just click on your picture and say edit avatar
And then just pick a picture from your photo library pick something cool
Mean I only have I only have two I have this one. Can you see it? And I got yeah, that's a generic one
I ain't trying to put this one up though, you know, let me see I ain't trying to put
Don't know. I don't know how to do any of that stuff. So so do you have an iPhone or an Android?
Okay, so that's cool
So if you so when you came up here, right?
Because everything's different and Apple just made a new like stream yard thing
So when you're looking at your screen
Does it have a picture of you underneath and it says you're in the show?
Yeah, yes, I can see that. So if I say edit avatar I can show you some shit. There you go
Yep, click edit avatar and then do you see the options? It says take a picture, you know pick from your photo library and all that
So now you can you can click photo library and you can pick one that you have in there
Or you can take a picture right now, you know look at Shawnee goes right back to the white one
Oh, fun.
Look at Baby Spunky.
This is from a long time ago.
Yeah, change it up if you want.
I don't want to save it on show.
I like mixing.
And then you can save, it saves a lot on there too.
You can see like, this is my regular one that I have up.
That's the painting Raphael.
That's the school of Athens painting.
Oh yeah.
This is Baby Spunky.
Look at that. Oh, wow. Hold on. Hey, psyche. You still here. Can you put that bit nice job psyche? Oh
Wait a minute. Is that your child or is that when you're young?
That's me. That's me when I was young. Oh, wow, that's adorable
Yeah, is that is that your real hair color or no my real hair color is black
But that's just a very young picture of me
cool
And then this one's Josh Allen. I'm a big buffalo bills. Oh, yeah, Josh Allen. Why not, right? That's him hurtle and look at him hurtle and
I really thought you know wow
Yo school don't come out. I'm gonna tell you my two favorites. You're looking at another young spunky picture
This is less young go back site. Let's go see put spunky up
Nice job site. That's like 10 years ago. Wow
That's blonde Jamie. What do you think? That's 30 year old spunky. Mm-hmm. It's pretty, right?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I still put my monkey in this spunky. Oh
Okay, so
I had a draw my soulmate picture done
And and I said show me my soulmate looks like and this is what they showed me and it does kind of good boy all
Oh, look is that
Kind of funny Justin. Do you see it? All right? I'm gonna show you guys. So Jamie
I didn't tell you this with my girlfriend and I don't go to school. Hold on. Hold on school the best
Yo, Tom Brady and hold on. Hold on. Wait till you guys see this picture. So my my I'm single again
Look at that picture of me. Look at that
That's me and my ex-girlfriend
That's me. We're at the wedding. We're at the wedding of different you was fried school you look crazy
He was he was lit. He was fried
You see me dipping her
Not it we done we done done's
You see if I can find
Now you got to
White dots got some bullshit tux right now
This was my favorite look at me look at me and my grandmother. Oh
My grandmother best look at that one
Put that one up see that one
Yeah, I
Love my I take here
You know now you're still with you
They have free money to school I
Don't know what happened probably press the button. I did that accidentally
What's going on we got genius cowboys and we got spunky
There we go
I don't know what happened. It's it's too much for the phones to you know, like the phones
Yeah, it's just like they keep changing everything. So stream yard now
Like you weren't used to be able to chat like on the iPhone
You see all my boys Sean he always
What's in the middle of guys school arm? I'm sorry. There's my back cuz look for me. I love you. It's all right
You're my real big baby
i'm not going live bro like for me when i do that it's not bad it's just like
like some shit comes to my mind right away you know niggas hit you in the head sometimes
like i'm gonna forget it you know so bro this weekend i promise you guaranteed bet on Shakur
stevensson he's gonna win a decision right put him for a decision and um there's another fight
Birlango versus that Hamza Shirazut. I don't know. There's a that's a political fight
It could go either way
But but Shakur is winning 100% like I guarantee you know I'm saying like I'll put my my mama's life on it
And they're like he's winning you for me. He's winning
so
bet that bro cuz that's what I'm about to do and
I'm missing another fight, but I can't remember what's on my head though
All right, you think about that Jamie look at me when I was 23
How bad you said how Jersey Shore does that look Jersey Shore doesn't that look so Jersey Shore?
Yeah
God
Let's see what else we got
Mm-hmm. Oh, this is a good one. This is my grandfather and grandmother in 1946
Married, this is their marriage photo
This is a really good one because he looks exactly like me it's scary
Fuck is happening right now
Come on bullshit. Sorry guys. We do this again
Here we go. Okay
Done this should just work
Okay, oh my god, this is so annoying
Really frustrating sometimes so this but it could be a lot worse. I could be in Africa with no food
Seriously, that's what I always do when I say something's here we go look at that picture
That look does that look like me
Little bit a lot of it if you knew me like Roman off. It's like exactly like me my grandfather
Man fuck all that we talking boxing with school
I lost money yesterday, man. I dropped like 100 bucks today's the new day. Oh fuck that shit
All right, so just what I want you to do is is this just tell me the two guys that are fighting
And I'm gonna write it down that you said don't go crazy
Okay, cuz you'll take over the panel
I know you and just tell me the two guys that you were saying when is it this weekend? Yeah
What's the names?
Shakur Stevenson
Okay, is he gonna win hundred percent? I'll pull my life on it. Okay, Stevenson and and he's verse who
He's gone against William Zepeda
Zepeda Z-A-P-E-T-A and
We're gonna do 35 and do you think he's gonna knock him out? No, no, it's gonna go to distance
Okay, Stevenson the distance gotcha
Gonna be a technical fight to the end 12 rounds
I want to check out right now, FanDuel.
Oh, I figured out how to edit my headline.
There you go.
Can anyone see it?
Oh, I can't, I'm in FanDuel right now.
Can anybody else see what she's doing now?
Because I'm looking at this, of course, Stevenson.
I guess someone saw it.
I was asking, let's see, Boxing.
Let's see what we got, Boxing.
I don't see Shakur Stevenson. Oh
Got it Shakur Stevenson William Sakura got it. Okay, so
Yes, Stevenson's minus twelve hundred bro. We'll see we can't just do that by decision
But hold on hold on. Let's see what happens
Okay, let me let me go back
Method of victory will the fight go the distance
yes in minus 260 so everybody says that okay Shakur Stevenson KO slash TKO is
plus 250 but look at Shakur Stevenson by points the decision is minus 220 bro
that's that's not good odds I don't want to bet that because it's really gonna
happen exactly I need round betting I need knockout in a round you know
Yeah, he's just it's just not that it's he's not that type of fighter. You know what I'm saying like he's yeah
He's more of like a hidden don't get hit. I know what you mean. I know what you mean
But like I need I bet like this if you bet a
Like a hundred dollars, right? Well, how much is a thousand dollars?
So if you bet a thousand so if you bet a thousand dollars, but I'm not gonna
but if you bet a thousand bucks on um let's see method of victory hold on
give me a sec I'll go to popular cuz that knockout bro I'm probably like he's not
gonna stop him bro I'll show you so she goes Stevenson by rounds if I bet 1,000
would win 454 so you know it's like it's just because they're not given free
money they're not trying to get free not because it's my yeah that's what's
good that's what's gonna happen you know we should do football up here and
during the season to what do you want to do the AOC you know in college league
fantasy league
So, I'm in my own fantasy, but you know what would be fun, Janie?
If we do a King of the Hill in Psyche's, like in Psyche's panel?
Yeah.
You know how to do that?
You know how to do King of the Hill?
No, I'll tell you so I'm gonna talk to psyche about this in king of the hill
You pick one team to win in the first in the first week, right?
Yeah, I pretty good. I've been pretty much right the whole three years. I mean fucking my homes, right? But you know
I'm sick of you know, you know school if I hold on hold on let's finish the king of the hill convo
OBJ OBJ hold on
So if you pick a team Jamie like if say you pick Kansas City to win
There's no points or anything like one and then if they win you move to the second week
And then you can't pick Kansas City again. Oh, yeah, and if anybody loses they're out
You know, so yeah, that would be fun, right? Well, you know what our division sucks. I mean, we have dad
He's not a pocket passer. He's not a runner. So at least, you know, you got
Josh Allen, right? So well, we don't have that wait. Dak is Dallas though
I know what I'm trying to say is I would never say Dallas and my division because eagles are really good. Oh
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're gonna go FC you're gonna go AFC
Totally agree with you totally yeah the eagles are me and you have any respect for me in our love. Unwrench the bitch, please
Yeah, I think it's Ali. I think it's a lot of hours with you and my dog died and she's talking shit on my dog and saying that I
Said my dog died and now she's going on about the dog dying in the chat. Just fucking unrenched the bitch
That's all I asked like he okay. Yeah, I did but okay because I told her to stop and she she did it
She won't stop. So yeah, she won't stop. She won't stop. I don't know
No problem with anyone ever you never see me get crazy on here my fucking dog died. I don't appreciate it
I didn't even talk about it on panel. I never mentioned my dog on panel
Only God he knew about it because he had a phone conversation with Justin and this bitch is bringing it up. I want it done
Okay, okay. Yeah, I
Mean, I told the I told everyone to stop arguing like way earlier and it's like
Yeah, and as they got appropriate to bring up animals
I never even brought up on your panel because it's a downer man
I was fucking suffering so bad about my dog dying
I never once brought it up on your panel because I never tried to bring your shit down at all and
And now we want to like harp on me and chat
Yeah, I know I'm sorry, but I didn't I was like it was I was really they trying to figure out I know
Who she says she is because there's nobody
Who would be a normal human being that doesn't know me that does not want to fuck with me
That would not want to like bring up my dog dying like this is crazy
Sorry guys, hey, okay, you have to be sorry
Here your psyche again, I just got to say you're doing awesome man. Well, thank you so much
It's psyche. It's like I just wanted to say you're a rock star
Rockstar by a bunch of people that troll you and I never did
I
Only came in here to support you and love you and fell in love with you completely and
Stopped all the shit that all the shit probably stopped because of me honestly, so I just want you to know that
Okay, thank you. I really appreciate it
Yeah, you've always been always like, you know, you came in it was like really thank you. I respect you so much
I would let you suck my penis. I think
Because that's what I thank you. Don't catch the hurt. You're welcome
Like he stopped all that shit. Yeah, we stopped all that shit like he's like he you're the best like he
Like he I don't you know, I don't know where my life would be without you right now psyche psyche
Hey, what's going on everybody
Psycho. What's up, brother? I thought you were Michael real quick. You know that guy Michael. No, I'm just glazing psyche right now
Don't don't interrupt. No, no, you're the bet. You're cool, man. You're cool
My glazing session right now don't interrupt. Okay. I'm muting up glaze away
Everybody good
Everybody
Dude, he's edging right now, too
Oh, my God.
He's like, you remember Prince James' name?
He changed his name into a wolf.
Yeah, I did.
Sorry, that's my vibrator. I'm sorry. Oh
My god
That's awesome. Yeah, I'm streaming. I'm streaming on chatter bait right now. Oh my god
You guys don't see anything
Because the same screen name I'm gonna go sign on biggie. Can you tell me you can donate you can donate to
So many eggs to you what is a better bait? What is that? I don't really know
There's some shit basically
Are you pretending like you don't know what chatter because I knew that someone was gonna say that
Do you know that I learned what the word docs meant just like in the last year?
Well, that's one thing, but everybody knows what Chatterbait is.
Everybody knows what Chatterbait is.
You're a liar.
I would really like to know.
Well, let's see chatter bait, right master bait chatter bait. I imagine it's like a cam session website, right?
This guy goes on chatter bait a lot. Like I'm gonna look it up right now. You must be on chatter bait a fucking lot
So what are you doing on Chatter Bay? I stream on Chatter Bay and I have a device attached to my penis and you can
Know my penis wait, can I pay a certain amount like vibrate your penis? That's exactly what it is. Yes
I'm gonna write the stars big old banner in honor of 4th of July to your penis right now
Okay, I'm gonna go donate it just didn't even have a Wikipedia page to tell you what it means
I'm pretty good at being a keeping a straight face.
Usually pretty good to tell when people are trolling and not but I'm not trolling.
I
Was spelling it wrong
Sorry, it wasn't chatter me
Guys it was a flirty diamonds chat. I'm sorry, and he showed his butthole there
Yes, you did oh my god
Wait, what'd you say?
Hotternaught.com.
Do you remember that from yesterday?
I remember the Hotty and the Naughty.
I remember the Hotty and the Naughty movie.
Hottyandnaughty.com.
Yeah.
What about, uh, did you ever remember the horror movie,
uh, House of Wax?
Do you remember that?
Yeah.
That's an underrated man. Yeah, it's it's with Paris Hilton
Yeah, it's underrated a great job. I see I'm gonna I'm gonna disagree with you
I think she did a great job
There's a lot of movies that are underrated because yeah fire one two and three is the best
Which one which one hair fire one? I never saw it and I love movies. Oh, yeah
And then psyche when we first got started you could fall
Oh, that's one you know what that's so funny that you just said follow that bird because I loved that movie as a kid and the
First time I went on psyche's page. That's what he was talking about
Mm-hmm. He picked it. It's fucked up that movie right all the shit that they wouldn't show like that cuz all the you remember was like the
Orphanage and they weren't allowed to be yeah, there was a lot of symbolism in that like
Yeah, I was like was just picking that out after you know like a black kid can't be with a white kids family
That's what they were like showing on there and then you know
What was it like they were
It was the dodo birds. I know I've seen it a thousand times
Remember they hadn't painted in blue they paint. Oh, yeah
Yeah, and then they had the two guys that were bad, you know, and they yep, they put them in there
Oh, it's sex trafficking, but it was like an exactly. I didn't want to say it, but you just pointed it out
Perfect that at one time. I think you're perfect. You're absolutely right
I was pissed off about the, was it the P Diddy verdict, but I knew that was going to happen.
The Rico charge wasn't going to stick.
I'm sick.
Yeah.
And I was disgusted with the Idaho 4.
You know what? I want to ask you something. Do you think that they put Rico charges out now to like like they just throw them out
To everywhere, you know and people keep beating them
So I think that they should stop
You know if I was if I was Kaylee's dad and the bailiff was out of the way
Yeah
You know, you know the case I can hear it. Do you know the case? Good. I do know the kid. I followed it and I was in a
school
Yes, Shawn. Yo, free the phones man, free the members, free all the guys, you know what I'm saying? Lockdown. Yeah, peace to the gods, peace to the OGs, but fuck P. Diddy.
No, free, free all, fuck, no, fuck P. Diddy. I'm talking about free all of the kids that are locked up right now.
Yeah, no, I know, I know. That made the wrong decision. But he fucking took kids, he's a fucking piece of shit.
I'm talking about real gangsters, bro. You know what I'm saying?
No, don't free him. Keep him locked up.
Do your gangster shit in prison, big homie. Oh, you know what I'm saying. They not nigga
Nah
Oh, free them. Nope. Nope and the justice. Nope. Don't free no gangsters. Let them do their gangster shit in prison
Thank you for the hostess shit
I'm gonna fuck them off. You want to do your gangster shit and they stay in prison
Yeah, I second that I second that well said we are here freedom
Kendrick Lamar graduated sixth in his class Compton High School and graduated sixth in his class
Damn
4.1
Unweighted GPA. I like how normally that wouldn't be that impressive but because it's Kendrick Lamar. It's impressive
Because I know but nobody ever brags. Oh, I was six
But think you know what is impressive is about the environment that he was in in Compton High School
And that he was six in the class because there's a lot of things
Do you know what I mean by that means that he's probably that number probably means less than it sounds like it does
That's what that means. No, it means more
man six six out of what other performing students six out of five like so
there's 500 kids that graduating in the class and he was six out of 500 you know
I mean valedictorians one salutatorians two he was six six yeah yeah he never
got a grade lower than an a all he got was a and a pluses from eighth grade to
twelfth grade
I learned more about suppressed African American history from him than I did in college.
I was a history major and I learned more from him in his lyrics.
Yeah.
Wow.
That just means that you're a fucking idiot.
You know that, right?
You're right, though. I agree.
Because it makes me feel sad that I learned about Black Wall Street, and when I was 28. You know what I mean?
I'm an idiot. I shouldn't have known about that when I was 18, so you're right. That's what it makes me feel like.
You got ripped, though.
Just makes me feel like, yeah, you're right. I totally agree. Like, the education was a fucking rip-off.
You told- I totally agree.
That's why I'm glad that I paid for the degree that I have.
Yeah.
And I didn't spend one moment in a classroom.
I'm with you, bro because you know what you're smarter than anybody else for doing that
I mean serious. I ain't trolling you if I wanted to troll you I would
All right now that I told everyone off to my life and lying to bed
All right, nice we heard check the chat for the rest. Good night. Bye
Adios. Good night
That's right. I didn't I didn't even start trolling yet
It would be so easy if I wanted to.
I like Ziggy, man.
I fucked out when it was.
It was like a month or two ago, though,
but he came up here and you were hamming Ziggy
and you had, I had to mute up because I spit out my fuel.
I was laughing so fucking hard at you.
And you were like, let's go, motherfucker.
And you were yelling at somebody up here.
And I started laughing.
I was eating steak and I spit it across the room, bro.
I spit all the butt out.
You just, bro, you were like, let's fuck it.
You know, when it was actually, it was when that night
that somebody shot somebody in Vegas.
Do you remember that?
Yeah.
That was then I think it was Vegas.
Like it was somebody who was on camera and the person got shot.
And you know, well, Sin City, Manny.
Who? I don't know.
But we from the you had me fucking ballin, bro.
I don't know. I wasn't like cheering anything like that
You were hammered bro, and one person was trying to talk about that Vegas thing and you just had I was crying, bro
He's funny as fuck, bro
People just they're so stupid right sake like
You're like you could tell when somebody's trying to troll you know what I mean and they'll take your shit
So seriously, and I'll just laugh my motherfucking ass off at that shit
Yeah
Yeah, have you guys ever seen um, yeah
You know that's you know that yeah, I see that you're right. It's funny. Yeah, I see that
That's just crazy. It's fucked up. I was telling Jamie about that before you're talking about the abacrombie documentary
That's what he's talking about Jamie. Yeah, dude. Yesterday. I was hearing fireworks
The fireworks that I was hearing it sounded like
Witches laughing. Oh
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's the cackling. That's the cackling witch
company
Is that a new is that a new thing because I feel like I've never seen this before they they bought out
You know the banana peel fireworks, you know that when they look like banana peels when they blow up and it's like they come out I
Don't operate right. I don't operate fireworks. I don't either. I
Know what you're talking about though
You Jamie
Hey, where'd they go? I don't know
Just sitting backstage for a little bit they are yeah
I talked to you. You know, uh, I you're okay. Uh, who's on beat is right now?
You're on what? You know who's on beat is right now?
No
It's okay. Okay. How are you? Okay. Good. How's things going? Good. What are you doing? You put them back state?
Hello
Sorry a lot
Where's Jamie girl, I don't know if she went but she probably went to check on something
Hope she was back soon. Yeah, Jamie is good
Hey, Jamie come back
Yeah, Jamie come back
Saw it does work. Hey, there she is. She's there. Come on over here, Jamie
Yeah, oh wow this chat was just wild
Hey, are you okay in the chat still? I mean, it's like I can't like
You just can't what are you what's wrong? Hello, what what's wrong?
What did you say?
I'm talking about Hannah in the chat like I kind of threw her the wolves good taking away her wrench
And I hope she's still there because she but she was saying those like wrong stuff
Crazy
she was attacking uh she's attacking spunky
but about her dog about her dog and stuff which is not good
that doesn't sound nice i told her to stop twice but oh i don't know site what happened
no are you okay you're not always up here this long that's why i was like whoa
He asked me you've got a different channel. I don't I don't know why
But I shouldn't have just said that Jamie because I haven't been around in about a month
So I don't even know if you have been up here, you know, ah
Yeah, I don't know what he's talking about how many
I have the legal amount five
There's a five is the legal limit. It's just so sad that you have to lead with that because people attack you for that shit
That sucks, you know, so the legal limit in California is fine
I feel so bad for you. No, it's an image and redondo. It is redondo or in your county
And no, I sit in the city this particular city, but I don't know if it's a county
Remember when people attacked him Jamie about coming cats he had
Yeah, not me. What are why we told you of course not of course not
But it's just so sad that he has to say, he's like programmed to lead with that to
Siggi. I have the legal amount. That's what he says first. Like that sucks.
Yeah, you can have him in many castes you want. Okay, so bad for you, psyche.
When the people with the pizza boxes.
well, then he's like wasn't I just they kind of just like tell the pizza people to go away
Nothing like I mean there's a lot worse threats and I know I just told some saying is I felt bad for you
I watched that old thing go down and I felt I mean it wait. What are you talking about? Oh
When I got like yeah, I got like yeah, I got like
Seven pizzas sent in a day or something remember sticky when he was like were they paid for no no, they were like
I'm saying I would I would say like you know
Can you guys at least like pay for like pay for that?
That's what I said, that's what I always said.
That was my, that was my...
And then psyche, you know what you could do with that and then what you could do.
psychies you when they ordered quadruple and chovy and pineapple pizza
Then you just then you just eat it
I'm still gonna eat it
I would have eaten it even if it was probably disgusting
They're gonna order pizza with
Nothing on it
I mean, I'm just dough extra undercooked undercooked dough.
That's what you bought.
Your body looks like sick. OK.
It's like, did you know without the sauce on it, that's what it is.
It's great. Yeah. Well.
What would you do? What would you do if because he would be on panel, you know,
live streaming and then there'd just be a knock at the door. Everybody could hear
it. This poor kid, this poor kid's like, is it pizza? Is it paid for? Someone's
like, no, no, sir. He's like, leave, just leave. They just kept knocking on your
door, right? Maybe like, psyche.
There's a pizza for you like this is pizza for you. It's not paid for
This is Alex. No, what really made me mad is when they were gonna harm the cats
Oh, I know
You got both sides of the McQueen you got Alexander when he paid for that food for you remember and you ate it
And then it was like the next day that all this happened after giving my address and stuff
You're echoing brother, I know
But that's that's the difference between Alexander and McQueen, you know, that's the difference
Yeah
Because I came with Alex, you know, I came with
With Alex and summer to your channel
Shout out to summer that's not in here right now. Yeah, you can see your name. You can see ish on my that's the crew
That's the ish crew. Yeah, and any
Money ish and Wanda if you ever go to Wanda's channel, I don't know if you've ever been there, but yeah Wanda woman
That's the it's a great
It's all the same people easy
Summer and Christine Christine's my mom, you know, she's yeah
That's my mother
Christine's cool. Yeah. Yeah, that's my mom
And it was so cool cuz on Samans thing I text I said Christine's my mom and someone's like
What and then Christine goes I am school's mother and everyone's like what wait a minute, you know, the people are just so funny like
Easy get up here
What ledges down that ledge in the comments. Come on, let's
All the other is Wando was gifted membership he said come up here, let's please don't
Oh, Marcy's dead too. Well, you know Marcy Marcy get your ass up here Marcy and don't it's so cool
If Marcy if you write another thing in the chat and you're not up here
I'm gonna I'm gonna ignore you Amanda
I didn't I was looking for Tara one night and I found psych and I said I could help him
He only had three subscribers
I said I could build this channel. I like it. I like like uh, you were the first person I talked to when I came
And Teresa I wish Teresa my traveling gypsy. Yeah
Yeah, you would have for I feel so lucky right now. It's just me and you on here. This is crazy
The people who's so funny though
Thank you God's be the guy's so mad at me when uh
You saw that she got so angry at me and I was like, you know like what is wrong with you?
You're so like jelly, but why you don't I don't care if you like Jamie. It's like, okay. Yeah, I got the fuck
Let's go for a ride. I'm gonna go for a ride
Yeah, I just uh, I'm going right now for a ride
Are you are in Sykes discord? You're not I don't do I don't do discord. I don't do Facebook
I don't do don't listen any of that you should go to Sykes discord. I'm in there
No, I mean, I don't do I don't do that. I don't have a discord. I don't have a Facebook
Don't do the cell phone thing. I always do I do Google chat, you know
That's how I talk to like my friends on you that you know that Google chat. Oh
No, I really don't know. Oh boy. Do you have a Gmail?
Yeah, yeah, so like if you so you have like the gmail app on your phone if you downloaded Google chat
It's connected to your email, and then you make you can do audio calls and video calls that way
So like when I speak to Christine, I speak to somebody I use that I use g-chat
Mmm. Yeah
Mmm, we'll see if Sean P shows up on Thursday
I gotta go into Brooklyn all right. Let's go for a ride to get my cheese
God, I'm getting so old. I have to I just got a pair of cheaters for the first time
You know the glasses, you know what they are cheaters
Mm-hmm. Yeah, just
So now I got an optometrist
Appointment and I'm getting the new contacts so I can see close and fall with them so fucking old
Marcy was up. I think the other night up
It did Marcy right again in the chat because I'm not looking and I'm gonna be so pissed at her if she did
Yeah, she saw ha ha all Marcy. I'm pet. Oh
Yeah, school makes us go back into you. Oh, I'm pissed at you Marcy
Get your ass up here. I
Don't either Athens come on Mars. What are you doing?
Love Gotti's name. He's got such a good name. Yeah, it's a great name
That's the haircut that I had for like ever because did you ever see that?
And I'm going outside you ever see that I'm
Growing up Gotti dark, you know that reality show. Yes, I'm TV. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it was in like the like the
I'm a huge challenge fan. Oh
Yeah, road rules. Are you talking about? Yeah, totally. That's like how we how old do you don't have to say if you don't want it?
Okay, don't worry about it. Don't worry about it. It's all good. Um, yeah, but you know, I like the challenge because Veronica
Rachel
They were down where I you know during the challenge and everything
doing some kind of
Meet and greet a while back and it was cool. That's cool. Those are the OGs. You say while back
God he's funny
a little bit
Kid I'm running through my sprinklers because all my you know the automatic sprinklers on my front yard. Can you hear him a little bit? Yeah
Shit I'm getting doused. Oh shit. I just got doused
me or not am I dead? I can hear you. Wow it's dead.
Yelp.
It was funny when he said uh Sweetcorn Berkeley like
you know once went to the Eagles was that not a
game changer? Jamie can you hear me?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm going to the store. Oh, okay
I'm going to the store
I'm gonna get some more you're gonna go to the store sick. Okay. No, I'm not
Mimicking I'm going to the store. I'm going to the store
You're not even gonna ask if I want anything. Well, I was gonna ask if you want. Yeah, what do you think?
You're not gonna ask if I want anything
I just did twice just did twice. Let me get a kiwi snapple
Oh, what kind of apple and they and they let's plain chips
Salt chips you want. I got them kettle cooked. You want the kettle cook one?
Yeah, yeah
I got your Cape Cod. Oh, what do you know what? You got the glass. You got the glass bottle. It's even better
I love the glass bottle Snapple. Yeah, you want Snapple Apple?
Like a mango. Yeah, whatever you got. I like that half and half if it's not kiwi
I like the kiwi strawberry. He likes kiwi strawberry. That one's good too. That's mine
And I love it under the lids
They mean a lot like in and out if you look under like napple facts
The list is gonna say you know how that worked
It was like one one out of like four were true not all of them were true. That was great, right?
All right, how about some coke?
You want some coke? I'm about to do some coke
Sure
Pepsi Coke heard that yeah, you got a Boston cream Dona
You know that's where it's at. Oh, you know what? That's what I'm gonna get ready. I'm gonna get a chocolate eclair
I'm gonna go get let me check my 7-Eleven. Let me get like maybe four cannolis
Market has his own business and I help them with all that stuff on a market day. Yeah
But you know what they haven't it's it outlet out down here because it's out of San Francisco in Oakland
So it's it is like a ice cream and graham cracker around it. It's really good
You should look for it that's her talking Mike Mike. It's just turn
What?
Yeah, go ahead buddy. I'm leaving
Yo Nikki there is just to talk to you about
So my you turn my graham cracker and ice cream. Yeah, it's called. It's it's the outlet is down here, California
It's it's
Yeah, they're they're San Francisco based
Well, that's not and they ship to the ship
Get them all our walmarts have them. I'm not worried about it, but you know what I mean? It's really neat
We ship them in dry ice containers
Mitten chip
Strawberry and I think one is
Cocoa like do they have cookies and cream? No
You could look at it
Yeah, I know
They can make a cheesecake. I'm out one that reason. I'm you're out. You're out
Yeah, I think there's a few other brands
That does the nationwide shipping thing that probably better in all honesty
Oh, yeah
I'm trying to remember one
Let me see. Let me look it up. I'll see if I could find you the name of it
But there's one maybe you know it too, but it's like probably better. No honesty
You see this shit
Maybe I don't find it
Have you had graders?
No, what is that? No, I got it. I found it the brand. It's called graders
That that's ice cream I'm gonna get if I'm gonna do nationwide shipping
That's the ice cream that I'm gonna get
Yeah
It's gonna be like that
Look up, it's it's two they're good it's it's mm-hmm. That's that's crazy
We like donuts, so you think about donuts no
Yeah, your mic sounds really bad all of a sudden
It's a Bluetooth. It just hooked up on my car automatically. Let me just shut it off
Bunny all these people have rain in 96 98 and we're gonna be a hundred and five next week
It's it's made in 1928 San Francisco
Does that feel does that sound bad as big that sounds about one hundred billion times better
All right, then we're good
Yeah, you rock solid
1928 is crazy
Are we going for a ride? We'll go to the store and get some donuts. We don't take we're gonna take a psyche for a ride
That's right. We're gonna take them for a ride
Rocky it's like you mean sticky. You're gonna take you for a fucking ride little boy
Sick has the personality of a dog
Ah, sickie school, man.
Sickie school, you just can't take it too seriously, man.
Way back, bro.
Maybe in some way, sure, but not in every way.
Now you ain't no dog.
Definitely not.
I'm a dog.
I'm a dirty dog.
Fuck that. That's a fact I'm a dog. You'd be like a lion
You know like how the lion just laughs you know
You know what I mean? How he just sleeps and he just like eats when he has to do I mean
I'm an apex predator. I'd be a para green Falcon. That's what I am
I'm like he's definitely a lot and so he's definitely a lion. I mean Ziggie's definitely a lion like us Phoenix
Is that you your phoenix? Oh, yeah, like he is a gay queen
Like he's a giraffe bro. So he's a giraffe. I respect that
He's dead or an ostrich. So he's an ostrich
He's a gay ostrich gay pride ostrich gay pride rainbow colored
No, I think I heard I actually saw this news thing
It was like a few people were killed
Like I think Australians or something some tourists
were killed by a
Elephant because the elephant like ran him down
Their elephants is probably it's probably because they're the elephant babies nearby
An elf elephants are like normally not violent, but they're very protective of their young
Is it the females that do that I'm not sure I think probably both
Well, I don't know if it's like, you know how like the line a male lion like he doesn't do shit
Except for fight and fuck. That's all they do honestly. They just fight and fuck well that can be a useful rule
Yeah, yeah, that's like it's like a
Yeah, so like I'm a deer hunter, you know we go upstate and the bucks
That's all they do. They just try to take control of an area
So they come across an area and there's a couple of those and then they look for the other buck
And then they fight each other and if he kicks the other box ass then they're in control of the dose, you know
Did everybody go I have no idea Wow
Well, hello, Jamie. How are you doing? I am fine. I don't know what he's doing tonight. I
Don't know maybe he's trying to mix it up. I was actually coming to see what the hell Athens has been up to
He's been gone for a while he just came back. I must have been back in the stream then
Must be the slow part of the night
We streamed for 20 hours today, we tried
Chats where it's at then I
Thought he was Marcy
Okay, what's going on with the wrenches again? Are we going over this again?
Oh, did I miss something earlier? Did something happen?
Yeah, I guess that lady Hannah is attacking everyone.
Which lady? Crystal?
No, I like Crystal.
I was just saying Crystal be losing her shit though.
Hannah
Okay, I haven't heard about that one. What's Hannah been doing? I guess attacking everyone in chat
My turn Hannah, where you at?
It's not cool spunky lost a dog. Don't pick on them. Don't pick on anybody
Pick on me you already picked on everybody else damn. We want positive vibes here and no negativity
I got phone mo fear of being left out
Mmm
It's not cool though, you know what I mean, that's her dog has some respect
It's not cool
But I'll say you know, she's gonna fuck with everybody. I don't fuck with me, too
Yeah
I guess I guess somebody must have paid to get you kicked or something bruh
They can they can make money on if they want to kick me it's no problem
No, I think eight things and then might have got kicked
Oh
recite
Yeah, this like wants to make money and someone wants to kick me on I'm okay with that
So people have space up here, you know, it's no worries
They there's plenty of space though
Yeah
Well, I like to give people, you know chances to come up, you know and
visit
No, you're working the controls right now Jamie. No
I don't know nothing about that
It's like even the back stream working. Yeah, Marcy probably dropped signal going to the store
You're right and sig I think sig was going to the store
To get
Something to drink
Okay
Signal that's uh, that's a weird one
I guess so, Irby.
Psych, what are you doing tonight?
Oh, got it.
I can drop down and then come back up.
Marcy, you can go up.
Are you okay? Do you need time you need more people up here? It's okay
I think psyche was trying to his hand at trolling. Oh, we're back. We're back. We're back
I was going through Jamie withdrawal. I'm at the store right now. I was going through Jamie withdrawal back there, you know
Good. Good. I needed my Jamie
You're okay. No, no, I'm just kidding people would stop simping on Jamie
It's like anything you say nice to somebody like stop simping. It's like you cannot give a compliment to somebody
But my next is up
What's good, how are you?
That's my boy, I'm chillin man
Don't matter
What'd you say it doesn't matter you can do, you know, you know, I know I'm just messing around
Boy, I love that X that he's a good guy
He's a good
We'll be on this we'll be on the same wavelength him and I